<xml xmlns:s='uuid:BDC6E3F0-6DA3-11d1-A2A3-00AA00C14882'
     xmlns:dt='uuid:C2F41010-65B3-11d1-A29F-00AA00C14882'
     xmlns:rs='urn:schemas-microsoft-com:rowset'
     xmlns:z='#RowsetSchema'>
<s:Schema id='RowsetSchema'>
   <s:ElementType name='row' content='eltOnly' rs:CommandTimeout='30'>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_ID' rs:name='ID' rs:number='1'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='i4' dt:maxLength='4' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_LinkTitle' rs:name='Folder Name' rs:number='2'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_TitleDisplayRI' rs:name='Display Title' rs:number='3'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_BiographyRI' rs:name='Biography' rs:number='4'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='1073741823' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_ClubNameRI' rs:name='Club Name' rs:number='5'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_DistrictRI' rs:name='District' rs:number='6'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_RegionRI' rs:name='Region' rs:number='7'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_Image1PathRI' rs:name='Image 1 Path' rs:number='8'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_Image2PathRI' rs:name='Image 2 Path' rs:number='9'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_Image3PathRI' rs:name='Image 3 Path' rs:number='10'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_Image4PathRI' rs:name='Image 4 Path' rs:number='11'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_Image5PathRI' rs:name='Image 5 Path' rs:number='12'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_Image6PathRI' rs:name='Image 6 Path' rs:number='13'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_Video1PathRI' rs:name='Video 1 Path' rs:number='14'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_CountryNameRI' rs:name='Country Name' rs:number='15'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_CountryCodeRI' rs:name='Country Code' rs:number='16'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
      <s:AttributeType name='ows_DonorLevelRI' rs:name='Donor Level' rs:number='17'>
         <s:datatype dt:type='string' dt:maxLength='512' />
      </s:AttributeType>
   </s:ElementType>
</s:Schema>
<rs:data>
   <z:row ows_ID='768' ows_LinkTitle='BaekHoKimandKeumSoonOh' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Baek-Ho Kim and Keum Soon Oh' ows_ClubNameRI='Jeonju Jungang' ows_DistrictRI='3670' ows_RegionRI='Jeonrabug' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/BaekHoKimandKeumSoonOh/Kim Baek-Ho.jpg' ows_Image2PathRI='Donors/BaekHoKimandKeumSoonOh/Kim1.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='769' ows_LinkTitle='JongDukLeeandSuJungAn' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Jong-Duk Lee and Su Jung An' ows_ClubNameRI='Migeum' ows_DistrictRI='3600' ows_RegionRI='Gyeonggi' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JongDukLeeandSuJungAn/Lee Jong-Duk.jpg' ows_Image2PathRI='Donors/JongDukLeeandSuJungAn/Lee1.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='770' ows_LinkTitle='KwangSupKilandEumSookChoi' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Kwang Sup Kil and Eum Sook Choi' ows_ClubNameRI='Shin Gwangmyeong' ows_DistrictRI='3690' ows_RegionRI='Gyeonggi' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/KwangSupKilandEumSookChoi/Kil Kwang Sup and Eum Sook Choi.jpg' ows_Image2PathRI='Donors/KwangSupKilandEumSookChoi/Kil1.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='771' ows_LinkTitle='YongChaeKimandSaeBonChae' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Yong Chae Kim and Sae Bon Chae' ows_ClubNameRI='Gwangju-Hanam' ows_DistrictRI='3710' ows_RegionRI='Gwangju' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/YongChaeKimandSaeBonChae/Kim Yong Chae.jpg' ows_Image2PathRI='Donors/YongChaeKimandSaeBonChae/Kim1.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='772' ows_LinkTitle='DatoJimmyThawChayandBrendaLaiChengLim' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Dato “Jimmy” Thaw Chay and Brenda Lai Cheng Lim' ows_ClubNameRI='Kuala Lumpur Diraja' ows_DistrictRI='3300' ows_RegionRI='Kuala Lumpur' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/DatoJimmyThawChayandBrendaLaiChengLim/Dato Jimmy Thaw Chay and Brenda Lai Cheng Lim.jpg' ows_Image2PathRI='Donors/DatoJimmyThawChayandBrendaLaiChengLim/Lim1.jpg' ows_Image3PathRI='Donors/DatoJimmyThawChayandBrendaLaiChengLim/Lim2.jpg' ows_Image4PathRI='Donors/DatoJimmyThawChayandBrendaLaiChengLim/Lim3.jpg' ows_Image5PathRI='Donors/DatoJimmyThawChayandBrendaLaiChengLim/Lim4.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Malaysia' ows_CountryCodeRI='MY' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='773' ows_LinkTitle='CyrusSandVillooPoonawalla' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Cyrus and Villoo Poonawalla' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Cyrus Poonawalla is a prominent leader in the biotechnology community and holds a PhD from Pune University in India. He is the chairman of the Poonawalla Group, and in 1966 he established Serum Institute of India, which annually produces 1 billion vaccine doses for several diseases, including polio, measles, meningitis, and the flu. Serum Institute makes high-quality, low-cost vaccines available to underprivileged communities, and for this reason, Bill Gates recognized Cyrus as one of his Seven Vaccine Heroes of the World in 2011.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Cyrus has received many accolades for his work, including Padma Shri from the government of India for his contributions to the health field, the Award of Excellence in Inter-American Public Health by the Pan American Health Organization and Pan American Health and Education Foundation, and named Best Vaccine Executive of the Year, presented during the World Vaccine Congress Asia 2011. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Cyrus is internationally renowned for his achievements in horse breeding and racing and is also interested in designer cars and real estate. He was married to his late wife, Villoo, for many years, and together they have one son. Cyrus has donated to various charitable organizations worldwide, both personally and through Serum Institute of India, including gifts of vaccines worth more than $100 million. His contributions reflect his personal motto of “health for all with affordable vaccines.”&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='No-club' ows_DistrictRI='3131' ows_RegionRI='Pune' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/CyrusSandVillooPoonawalla/Poonawalla Cyrus.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='India' ows_CountryCodeRI='IN' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='774' ows_LinkTitle='CharlesE.andBarbaraR.Clemmons' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Charles E. and Barbara R. Clemmons' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Charles and Barbara Clemmons founded a company that produces software used at nuclear power plants in the U.S. and around the world. They are both now retired, but the company is still managed by the Clemmons family.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Charlie became a charter member of the Rotary Club of Seabrook in 1992. He has served as club secretary (1995-96) and president (1997-98) and held district positions including governor (2000-01), grants subcommittee chair (2001-02), Rotary Foundation committee chair (2002-04), and district conference presidential representative (2002-10). He also served Rotary as chair of the Water Resource Group and an RI president’s representative to the U.S. State Department to discuss extending Rotary to Cuba. Charlie is a founding trustee of the Rotarian Safe Water and Sanitation Foundation.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Barb also joined the Rotary Club of Seabrook, in 1993. She served as club president (2006-07), district alumni subcommittee chair (2007-09), and assistant governor (2008-10). Barb once led a Group Study Exchange team stationed in South Africa for six weeks. Her late parents, Herbert E. and Lenore S. Miller, are also members of the Arch Klumph Society.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;In 2006, Charlie and Barb founded The Second Wind Foundation, the financial arm of Rotary Books for the World, which ships educational materials collected by Rotarians in North America to developing countries.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Seabrook' ows_DistrictRI='5890' ows_RegionRI='Texas' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/CharlesE.andBarbaraR.Clemmons/Clemmons Charles and Barbara.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='775' ows_LinkTitle='YoungSukYoonandSeungJaCho' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Young Suk Yoon and Seung Ja Cho' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Young Suk Yoon holds a master’s degree in management from San Francisco State University in California. A businessman whose specialty is heavy industries and construction, Young Suk has held the chairman or CEO position at Daewoo Corporation, Daewoo Heavy Industries &amp;amp; Machinery Ltd., Korea Heavy Industries &amp;amp; Machinery, and Doosan Heavy Industries &amp;amp; Machinery. He is the founder and chairman of Heam Management Consulting. Young Suk has served as the honorary consul of the Republic of Uganda in Korea since 1991 as well as the chairman for both the Republic of Korea and Germany Economic Corporation and the Republic of Korea and Mongolia Economic Corporation. Young Suk is also the recipient of the Order of Industrial Service Merit Gold Tower from the government of Korea.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Young Suk joined the Rotary Club of Seoul Hangang in 1990. He became a member of the Seoul-Hoehyon club in 1996 and served as club president in 2004-05. Young Suk was governor of District 3650 during 2009-10. He also has served as district Annual Fund subcommittee chair (2010-11), district Permanent Fund subcommittee chair (2010-11), district Rotary Foundation chair (2012-13), and district fundraising subcommittee chair (2010-13). Young Suk will serve as a Rotary Foundation Trustee from 2014 to 2018.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Young Suk and his wife, Seung Ja, have two daughters, one son, and six grandchildren. The couple supports The Rotary Foundation through the Young Suk Yoon Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Seoul Hoehyon' ows_DistrictRI='3650' ows_RegionRI='Seoul' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/YoungSukYoonandSeungJaCho/Yoon Suk Yoon.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='776' ows_LinkTitle='DukSamLeeandHyunSukJang1' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Duk-Sam Lee and Hyun Suk Jang' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Duk-Sam Lee was born in Seoul, Korea. He has built a successful career in the manufacturing industry and is the CEO of Sunseong Company. Duk-Sam is also the chairman of the Jingeon High School Alumni Association, vice chairman of Jingeon Police Station’s Safety Assurance Foundation, and director of the Gyeonggi Province Chamber of Commerce and the Namyangju City Athletic Association. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Duk-Sam joined the Rotary Club of Namyangju-Jingeon in 2005. He has served as club president three times (2006-09). He served as assistant governor in 2010-11 and as district Annual Fund subcommittee chair in 2012-13. He enjoys working on service projects with his fellow club members, particularly projects assisting the elderly and providing home repair services to those in need.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Hyun Suk Jang, who is also a member of the Rotary Club of Namyangju-Jingeon, is self-employed. Duk-Sam and Hyun Suk have been married for more than 25 years, and they have a son and a daughter.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Namyangju-Jingeon' ows_DistrictRI='3600' ows_RegionRI='Gyeonggi' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/DukSamLeeandHyunSukJang1/Lee Duk-Sam and Hyun-Suk.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Chair Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='777' ows_LinkTitle='JulioandCarmenSorjs' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Julio and Carmen Sorjús' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Julio Sorjús was born in Bayonne, France. He studied law at the University of Barcelona and has spent most of his career as an attorney, although he has also worked as assistant general manager of an industrial bank. He joined the Rotary Club of Barcelona Pedralbes in 1983, and a year later he helped found the Rotary Club of Barcelona Condal, serving as its first president.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;An active proponent of the Rotary Youth Exchange program, Julio served as Spain’s national delegate for Youth Exchange activities for eight years. In 1991-92, he was governor of District 2210, and he sat on the RI Board of Directors from 1998 to 2000. While serving as chair of the Host Organization Committee for the 2002 RI Convention in Barcelona, Julio helped establish a promotional publication called España Rotaria, which later became an official Rotary regional magazine. He also served as vice chair of the Barcelona convention committee and chair of the 2007 Salt Lake City Convention Committee. Julio will serve on the Foundation’s Board of Trustees from 2012 until 2016.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Julio was a member of the PolioPlus National Advocacy Advisers Committee from 2002 to 2006, and he calls his experiences participating in polio-immunization campaigns in India and Mali the most important events of his life. Julio and Carmen have a named fund within the Endowed Fund and are charter members of the Bequest Society.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Barcelona Condal' ows_DistrictRI='2202' ows_RegionRI='Barcelona' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JulioandCarmenSorjs/Sorjus Julio and Carmen.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Spain' ows_CountryCodeRI='ES' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='778' ows_LinkTitle='MakotoandMisuzuKanasugi' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Makoto and Misuzu Kanasugi' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Makoto is a graduate of Keio University, where he studied economics. He began working at Yokohama Petroleum Co. Ltd. in 1984 as a director; by the time he became president in 1993, he had transformed the company into a multifaceted corporation. In 1991, he established YSL Solution and currently serves as a senior adviser. He is president and CEO of YSG Holdings Co. Ltd., which he established in 2012. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Makoto, whose father and older brother were also members of Rotary, joined the Rotary Club of Yokohama West in 1994, and he served as president in 2001-02. The governor of District 2590 in 2005-06, Makoto also has served as the district’s World Community Service chair (2003-04), RI Convention promotion chair (2004-05), representative to the Council on Legislation (2010), district conference presidential representative (2012-13), End Polio Now zone coordinator (2012-13), and Rotary coordinator (2013-16).
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Makoto’s wife, Misuzu, who retired from a career in the cosmetics industry, is a former member of the Yokohama West club. She still enjoys participating in Rotary activities with Makoto. Together, they support The Rotary Foundation through the Makoto and Misuzu Kanasugi Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Yokohama West' ows_DistrictRI='2590' ows_RegionRI='Kanagawa' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/MakotoandMisuzuKanasugi/Kanasugi Makoto and Misuzu.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Japan' ows_CountryCodeRI='JP' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='779' ows_LinkTitle='SuguruandKazuyoOmuro' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Suguru and Kazuyo Omuro' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Suguru, a graduate of the Tohoku University School of Medicine, is a surgeon. He began his career as an intern at Osaka University Hospital and joined the medical staff in 1976, while also serving on the faculty at the Hyogo College of Medicine Hospital. In 1976, Suguru also became the board chair of Showakai Daiichi Hospital, where he has been president since 2011. Outside of medicine, he is a board member of the Takarazuka International Tourism Association, vice president of the Takarazuka Chamber of Commerce, and a director of the Nishinomiya Taxpayers Association.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Suguru has been a charter member of the Rotary Club of Takarazuka Mukogawa since 1978 and was president in 1997-98. He has served as district governor as well as district Rotary Friendship Exchange chair, Rotary Community Corps chair, and finance chair, all in 2013-14. Suguru’s focus is on youth development, and he enjoys planning and participating in his club’s annual children’s baseball tournament.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Suguru’s wife, Kazuyo, works in pediatric medicine. In addition to participating in the activities of Suguru’s Rotary club, Kazuyo enjoys making stained glass. The couple has three children and three grandchildren. Suguru and Kazuyo support The Rotary Foundation through the Suguru and Kazuyo Omuro Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Takarazuka Mukogawa' ows_DistrictRI='2680' ows_RegionRI='Hyogo' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SuguruandKazuyoOmuro/Omuro Suguru and Kazuyo.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Japan' ows_CountryCodeRI='JP' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='780' ows_LinkTitle='IsakoFunaki' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Isako Funaki' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Isako is a graduate of the SANNO University School of Management, where she earned her bachelor’s degree in information management. A vibration and soundproofing engineer, she has been president of both Yacmo Corporation Ltd. and DB Co. Ltd.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Isako joined the Rotary Club of Tokyo Shirokane in 1995 and served as its president in 2004-05. She also was made an honorary member of the Rotary club of Makati South in 2014. Isako served as governor of District 2750 in 2013-14 and will serve as assistant regional Rotary Foundation coordinator in 2014-15.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;One of Isako’s favorite club projects involves a water project and the installation of solar panels on an island in Micronesia. She traveled to the island and helped with the installation. Isako hopes that Rotary will continue to increase the diversity of its membership in order to bring new ideas to clubs and districts. She supports the Rotary Foundation through The Isako Funaki Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Tokyo Shirokane' ows_DistrictRI='2750' ows_RegionRI='Tokyo' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/IsakoFunaki/Funaki Isako.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Japan' ows_CountryCodeRI='JP' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='781' ows_LinkTitle='TerrenceR.andBarbaraC.Caster' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Terrence R. and Barbara C. Caster' ows_ClubNameRI='La Mesa' ows_DistrictRI='5340' ows_RegionRI='California' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/TerrenceR.andBarbaraC.Caster/Caster Terrence and Barbara.jpg' ows_Image2PathRI='Donors/TerrenceR.andBarbaraC.Caster/Caster 1.jpg' ows_Image3PathRI='Donors/TerrenceR.andBarbaraC.Caster/Caster 2.jpg' ows_Image4PathRI='Donors/TerrenceR.andBarbaraC.Caster/Caster 3.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='782' ows_LinkTitle='RonaldL.andAndreaC.Morton' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Ronald L. and Andrea C. Morton' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Ron is the CEO of Morton Services Co. and has been an H&amp;amp;R Block franchisee since 1975. He is one of the largest franchise owners, with 65 offices in five states. A true entrepreneur, Ron also founded the Metro Driving School, was a franchisee of eight ACE America’s Cash Express, has owned a restaurant and an employment service, and was a teacher at a local college. Ron also served in the Peace Corps and has spent 10 years volunteering in public schools, serving as president of the booster club and running concession stands and sponsored athletic events.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Ron has been a member of the Sumter club since joining Rotary in 1994. Some of his favorite club projects are the Youth Exchange program and the annual auction to benefit Alzheimer’s organizations. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Ron and Andrea have been married for over two years. A homemaker and part-time receptionist, she is active in her church, volunteers at local food banks, and enjoys traveling with Ron to area Rotary events. Ron is the father of three, and Andrea has two children; they have a combined 13 grandchildren. Ron and Andrea support Rotary Peace Centers through the Ronald L. and Andrea C. Morton Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Sumter' ows_DistrictRI='7770' ows_RegionRI='South Carolina' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/RonaldL.andAndreaC.Morton/Morton Ronald and Andrea.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='783' ows_LinkTitle='GeorgeW.andKerstinE.Trowbridge' ows_TitleDisplayRI='George W. and Kerstin E. Trowbridge' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;George is a graduate of the University of Michigan. A banker, he has worked in New York City, San Francisco, and Stockholm, Sweden, in addition to Grand Rapids. He has also lent his professional skills to the United Way, and led the Grand Rapids Chamber of Commerce international business committee for three years.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;George has been a member of Rotary since 1969, when he joined the Rotary Club of Grand Rapids North. He served as club president (1972-73), Group Study Exchange district chair (1973-87), and district governor (1980-81, 1984-85, and 1986-87). In 1993, he joined the Grand Rapids club and has since served as district alumni subcommittee chair (2007-09) and district Foundation committee chair (2008-10). George’s fluency in Swedish has given him the opportunity to speak at district conferences in Sweden, where he has attended Rotary club meetings more than 150 times.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;George and his wife, Kerstin, a native of Sweden, have been married for over 47 years and have two children. A dedicated volunteer, Kerstin is a board member of the Swedish Council of America and a member of the Swedish American Heritage Society of Western Michigan, and she has taught Swedish for over 20 years.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Grand Rapids' ows_DistrictRI='6290' ows_RegionRI='Michigan' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/GeorgeW.andKerstinE.Trowbridge/Trowbridge George and Kerstein.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='784' ows_LinkTitle='ThomasA.andMarianBickerstaff' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Thomas A. and Marian Bickerstaff' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Tom earned a bachelor’s degree in international relations from Lehigh University, a master’s in business administration from the University of Pittsburgh, and a master’s in actuarial science from Northeastern University. Now retired, he was a regulatory life insurance actuary for over 40 years, helping to determine the financial condition of life insurance companies for state insurance departments across the United States. Tom has been a member of the budget and finance committees of both his homeowners’ association and his church.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Tom joined Rotary in 1981 as a member of the Rotary Club of Berlin, New Jersey, and has been a member of seven other Rotary clubs. He is currently a member of the Rotary Club of Snow Hill. Tom has served on many Rotary committees, including the District 7430 nominating committee (2002-02), budget committee (2001-03), and annual giving committee (2003-06), and he was chair of the District 7630 Paul Harris committee (2007-08) and Permanent Fund committee (2009-12).
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Tom has been married to Marian for over 18 years. Also retired, Marian was chief lending officer of a savings bank. Marian is a gifted artist who has been painting with oils since the early 1970s. She has served as president of the board of the Art League of Ocean City for two years.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Snow Hill' ows_DistrictRI='7630' ows_RegionRI='Maryland' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/ThomasA.andMarianBickerstaff/Bickerstaff Tom and Marian.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='785' ows_LinkTitle='ChristopherJ.McLucasandReynaL.Castillo' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Christopher J. McLucas and Reyna L. Castillo' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Christopher holds a bachelor’s degree in criminology from Dallas Baptist University and two master’s degrees (in criminology and public administration) and is a doctoral candidate in criminology at the University of Texas at Arlington. He is the owner of a national title insurance agency that is licensed in 39 states. Christopher was the 2013 chairman of the Boys and Girls Club of North Central Texas. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Christopher joined the Rotary Club of Arlington (Sunrise) in 2004 and served as club president in 2010-11, during which time he traveled to all four countries that were then polio-endemic. He was a Group Study Exchange team leader to Brazil in 2012-13, and has served as assistant governor for three years. Christopher participated in his first National Immunization Day in 2004, before becoming a Rotarian, and has participated in six others since. He is currently the district liaison for the International Fellowship of Scouting Rotarians.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Reyna is a graduate of the University of Nevada-Las Vegas, where she studied business management. She is a licensed Texas real estate agent. She has been a board member of the Boys and Girls Club of North Central Texas since 2010. A member of the Highland Village club since 2009, she had her first Rotary experience in 2008 when she traveled to Chile as a Group Study Exchange team member. She has served as club president (2010-11), club membership chair (2012-14), and district alumni subcommittee chair (2012-14).&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Arlington Sunrise, and the Rotary Club of Highland Village' ows_DistrictRI='5790' ows_RegionRI='Texas' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/ChristopherJ.McLucasandReynaL.Castillo/McLucas Christopher and Reyna.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='786' ows_LinkTitle='AliceVirginiaWhite' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Alice Virginia White' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Alice holds a bachelor’s degree from the University of Kansas, a master’s degree from Fort Hays State University, and a doctorate from the University of Texas at Austin. She has had several simultaneous careers, including co-owning a wheat farm in Colorado, working on several social marketing campaigns for the state government of Texas, and working in educational administration. In addition, she has managed her own investments for over 27 years. Alice has been recognized for her accomplishments by numerous organizations, including Farm Future magazine, the Lubbock Chapter of the Association of Women in Communications, South Plains College Foundation, Texas Public Relations Society of America, and the Texas Department of Health.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Alice joined the Rotary Club of Lubbock in 2006. She has served as president of the club’s foundation (2013-14) and as district Foundation committee chair (2013-16). Her favorite club project is volunteering at the South Plains Food Bank.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Alice also blogs about volunteering in her community and is an avid supporter of organizations that foster and adopt cats; she herself has two cats and has fostered 146 cats and kittens in a 35-month period.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Lubbock' ows_DistrictRI='5730' ows_RegionRI='Texas' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/AliceVirginiaWhite/White Alice.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='787' ows_LinkTitle='GeorgeC.andWilmaC.Wheeler' ows_TitleDisplayRI='George C. and Wilma C. Wheeler' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;George holds a business and science degree from Oregon State University as well as a master’s degree in health care administration from George Washington University. His 21-year career as a U.S. naval aviator included assignments as an operational adviser and flight instructor with the Chinese (Taiwan) Air Force, commander of an aircraft squadron, and member of the chief of naval operations staff. Most recently, he worked for Presbyterian Healthcare Services, initially as a hospital administrator and then as vice president for human resources. George is also active in the community and served on the corporate board of Sun Health, an Arizona medical nonprofit.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;George joined Rotary in 1986 and was a member of both the Rotary Club of Moriarty, New Mexico, and the Sun City West club in Arizona before joining the Peoria North club. George was district governor in 1999-2000 and has served as a Council on Legislation representative (2003-04 and 2009-13), district grants subcommittee chair (2008-2012), district Permanent Fund subcommittee chair (2006-09), and district Rotary Foundation chair (2012-13). He enjoys working on club projects for youth services including RYLA, Interact, and Youth Exchange.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;George and his wife, Willi who is a retired registered nurse, have been married for over 51 years. When she is not participating in Rotary activities with George, Willi enjoys reading, traveling, and boating. She is active with her local church and participates in other volunteer work. George and Willi spend much of their time volunteering and traveling together for Rotary projects.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Peoria North' ows_DistrictRI='5490' ows_RegionRI='Arizona' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/GeorgeC.andWilmaC.Wheeler/Wheeler George and Wilma.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='788' ows_LinkTitle='BobC.andSylviaDanner' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Bob C. and Sylvia Danner' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Bob earned his bachelor’s degree in mechanical engineering at Clemson University, where he was a participant in the Reserve Officers’ Training Corps. After graduation, he served at the Wright-Patterson Air Force Base in Ohio, assigned to perform research and development for aviation programs. Later, he was involved in the testing of missiles that made possible the development of rockets that eventually launched the U.S. space program. For more than 40 years, Bob has been the owner of Bio-Cide International, an international chemical company that manufactures products for food sanitation, water disinfection, and eye care. He is currently Bio-Cide’s chairman.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Bob has been a member of the Rotary Club of Norman since 1977. Through his club, he has traveled to Peru and Honduras to teach small groups how to conduct business and how to grow crops. He is a strong supporter of projects that provide people with sources of clean water.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Bob and his wife, Sylvia, have been married for over 53 years and have two sons and five grandchildren. Sylvia is a member of the Bio-Cide International board of directors. She enjoys supporting Bob’s love of Rotary and has traveled with him to conferences in Texas, Thailand, and Portugal.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Norman, and Rotary Club of Norman-Sooner' ows_DistrictRI='5770' ows_RegionRI='Oklahoma' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/BobC.andSylviaDanner/Danner Bob and Sylvia.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='789' ows_LinkTitle='GregE.andPamK.Podd' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Greg E. and Pam K. Podd' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Greg is a certified public accountant and a personal financial specialist having operated his own practice since June 1979. He was also the President and owner of a very large metal fabrication firm for the telecommunication industry and an international healthcare software development firm.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Greg became a Rotarian in May 1982 and is a member of the Evergreen Rotary Club.&amp;nbsp; He has served a three-year term as a member of the Rotary International finance committee, a six-year term as a member of the Rotary International investment committee, a three-year term as the regional Rotary Foundation coordinator for Zone 27 and a three-year term as a regional Rotary International membership coordinator. He has also served as a Rotary International training leader at the International Assembly in San Diego in January 2010 and 2011 (where Pam and Greg also served as hospitality hosts), as a Rotary Foundation future vision training leader in January 2013 and as a Rotary coordinator facilitator in March 2014.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Greg is the recipient of the Service Above Self Award and The Rotary Foundation Citation for Meritorious Service Award.&amp;nbsp; Greg and his wife Pam have been married for over 38 years, and have three children.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Evergreen' ows_DistrictRI='5450' ows_RegionRI='Colorado' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/GregE.andPamK.Podd/Podd Greg and Pamela.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Chair Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='790' ows_LinkTitle='CharlesG.andNancyK.Frazier' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Charles G. and Nancy K. Frazier' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Chuck attended Kansas University and Wichita State University and later owned and operated portrait photography studios for 30 years. He is a member and past president of the Kansas Professional Photographers Association and served on the National Council of Professional Photographers of America for seven years, having won its National Award in 1986. A volunteer for the United Way of the Flint Hills, he has served as president, member of the board of directors, and member of the allocation committee.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Chuck has been a member of the Emporia Rotary club since becoming a Rotarian in 1979. He has served as club president (1986-87), district governor (1998-99), and regional Rotary Foundation coordinator (2004-07) for Zone 29. He and his family particularly enjoyed participating in the Rotary Youth Exchange program, sending their 16-year old daughter to Senegal and later visiting her in Dakar. That visitation gave Chuck a new sense of the world of Rotary and solidified his personal mission to help those in need. Chuck received the Citation for Meritorious Service in 2001, the Distinguished Service Award in 2006, and the Service Above Self Award in 2010.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Chuck and his wife, Nancy, have been married for over 45 years and have two children and four grandchildren. Before Nancy retired in 1997, she worked in photography retail sales. An avid genealogical researcher, she has published three family history books. Nancy has been an avid supporter of Chuck’s Rotary career, accompanying him on his Group Study Exchange and to two National Immunization Days in Ghana.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Emporia' ows_DistrictRI='5710' ows_RegionRI='Kansas' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/CharlesG.andNancyK.Frazier/Frazier Charles and Nancy.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='791' ows_LinkTitle='SirEmekaOffor' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Sir Emeka Offor' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Sir Emeka Offor of Abuja, Nigeria, is the group executive vice chairman of the Chrome Group, a major conglomerate based in Nigeria that has partnerships with companies in oil and gas, construction, and telecommunications. Until recently, he was the nonexecutive chairman of the board of directors of ERHC Energy Inc., a U.S.-based independent oil and gas company. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Offor has established the Sir Emeka Offor Foundation, a nonprofit based in Nigeria that seeks to alleviate the suffering of the less fortunate through philanthropic activities. In addition to supporting Rotary’s priorities, the foundation is working on a multiyear project to revitalize education in Nigeria and elsewhere in Africa by equipping libraries, schools, and universities with computers, textbooks, and library books.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Offor is a member of the Rotary Club of Awka G.R.A. and a member of the PolioPlus Fundraising Committee. Offor is Rotary’s largest donor from Africa, and in addition to his support of the PolioPlus campaign as a donor and polio ambassador, he supports several of Rotary’s areas of focus, including peace and conflict prevention/resolution, maternal and child health, and basic education and literacy.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Awka G.R.A' ows_DistrictRI='9140' ows_RegionRI='Anambra State' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SirEmekaOffor/Offor Sir Emeka.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Nigeria' ows_CountryCodeRI='NG' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Foundation Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='792' ows_LinkTitle='NicolasandAnnieLynn' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Nicolas and Annie Lynn' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Nicolas is a business professional with broad experience, having worked in furniture sales, realty sales, and the shrimp farming industry. He joined the Taipei East club in 2011. Although Nicholas is new to Rotary, he comes from a long line of Rotarians.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Nicolas has been married to Annie for over 26 years and they have three children. Annie is a former furniture sales professional. Together, they support The Rotary Foundation through the Nicolas and Annie Lynn Endowment Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei East' ows_DistrictRI='3520' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/NicolasandAnnieLynn/Lynn Nicolas and Annie.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='793' ows_LinkTitle='JudyYunYuLiuandKuangChinLi' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Judy Yun-Yu Liu and Kuang-Chin Li' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Judy is a graduate of the Taoyuan Institute of Technology, where she earned a degree in business administration. She has used her expertise in the research and design of rubber products by serving as a director at Ji-Zhan Machinery Co. Ltd. and as president of Ji-Chang Rubber Industry Co. Ltd. and Ji-Chang Heavy Industry Co. Ltd. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Judy is a supporter of the Asia Pacific Girl Scouts of Taiwan and an adviser to the New Taipei City High School and the New Taipei City Volunteer Fire Department’s 3rd Squadron.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Judy joined the Rotary Club of Sanchung Chianshi in 2000 and served as club president in 2006-07. She has also held several district-level positions, including volunteer committee chair (2009-10) and Major Donor subcommittee chair (2012-13). In 2009, Judy traveled to India to participate in a National Immunization Day.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Judy has been married to Kuang-Chin Li for over 41 years. He is the president of Ji-Chang Rubber Co. and Ji-Zhan Machinery Co. Ltd. The couple has three children and five grandchildren. Judy and Kuang-Chin Li support The Rotary Foundation through the PP Judy-Liu Endowed Rotary Peace Certificate Program Fellowship.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Sanchung Chianshi' ows_DistrictRI='3490' ows_RegionRI='Sanchung' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JudyYunYuLiuandKuangChinLi/Liu Judy Yun-Yu and Kuang-Chin Li.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='794' ows_LinkTitle='MouldYuSenLiandSuChuChen' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Mould Yu-Sen Li and Su-Chu Chen' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Mould is the founder of Shang-Chuang Co. Inc., a manufacturer of containers and dishes. He joined the Rotary Club of Miaoli Central in 2009 and served as its president in 2010-11. In 2013, he became a charter member and the first president of the Miaoli Sunshine club.
&lt;br&gt; 
&lt;br&gt;Mould is married to Su-Chu. Together, they support The Rotary Foundation through the Yu-Sen Li “Mould” and Su-Chu Lin Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Miaoli Sunshine' ows_DistrictRI='3500' ows_RegionRI='Miaoli' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/MouldYuSenLiandSuChuChen/Li Mould Yu-Sen and Su-Chu Chen.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='795' ows_LinkTitle='JackandJennyChu' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Jack and Jenny Chu' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Jack has worked since 1965 at an import and export company. He joined the Rotary Club of Taipei South in 1985 and served as club president in 1998-99. While president, he created the club’s Community Service Fund, which uses interest income to carry out community service activities. His favorite club project is working with Good Shepherd House, an organization that provides education facilities to teachers working with disadvantaged youths. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Jack and his wife, Jenny, have four children and six grandchildren. Jenny enjoys listening to music, reading, and participating in Jack’s Rotary activities. They support The Rotary Foundation through the Jack and Jenny Chu Endowed Rotary Peace Certificate Program Fellowship.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei South' ows_DistrictRI='3520' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JackandJennyChu/Chu Jack and Jenny.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='796' ows_LinkTitle='FashionShihYuanandEuniceC.Chou' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Fashion Shih-Yuan and Eunice C. Chou' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Fashion is a graduate of Tamkang University in Taiwan. He is the chairman of the board at Ensuey International Garment Co. Ltd., a manufacturer of women’s apparel. A charter member of the Taipei Tungteh club since 1998, he served as club president in 2004-05. His district-level positions include membership development chair (2007-08), assistant governor (2008-09), and Rotary Foundation information chair (2013-14).
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Fashion has been married to his wife, Eunice, for over 31 years. She works as a fashion designer and is interested in music, reading, and gardening. They have three sons and one grandchild. The couple supports The Rotary Foundation through the Shih-Yuan and Sih-Ying Chou Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei Tungteh' ows_DistrictRI='3520' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/FashionShihYuanandEuniceC.Chou/Chou Fashion Shih-Yuan and Eunice.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='797' ows_LinkTitle='AmySuMeiChangChenandChiuChingChang' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Amy Su-Mei Chang Chen and Chiu-Ching Chang' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Amy has spent most of her professional career working in the finance department of Da-Hsing Lighting Decoration Co., a company owned by her husband. On a 1995 visit to an elementary school in Hui-Zhou, Guang Dong, China, Amy was inspired to financially adopt 173 students, paying their tuition and related expenses until they graduated from the school.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Amy joined the Rotary Club of Panchiao Central in August 2011 and is currently a member of the New Taipei City Lily club. She has served as a club president (2011-12), district major donor chair (2012-13), and Paul Harris chair (2013-14). 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Amy has been married to her husband, Chiu-Ching, for over 29 years, and they have five daughters. Chiu-Ching is the CEO of Da-Hsing Lighting Decoration Co. The couple supports The Rotary Foundation through the Chang Chiu-Ching, Chang Chen Su-Mei &amp;amp; Families Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='New Taipei City Lily' ows_DistrictRI='3490' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/AmySuMeiChangChenandChiuChingChang/Chen Amy Su-Mei Chang and Chiu-Chign Chang.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='798' ows_LinkTitle='PuloWenYenChang' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Pulo Wen-Yen Chang' ows_ClubNameRI='Chung-Li North' ows_DistrictRI='3500' ows_RegionRI='Chung-Li' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/PuloWenYenChang/Chang Pulo Wen-Yen.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='799' ows_LinkTitle='JudyandJeffChang' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Judy and Jeff Chang' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Judy is a professional in the electronics industry and a co-founder of Ji-Cheng Co. Ltd., which designs parts for electronic equipment. She has been a member of the Taipei Pei-An club since 2000, serving as club president in 2013-14. Her Rotary interests include working on educational projects that help disadvantaged students. Judy’s most memorable Rotary experience was participating in a polio eradication service project in India.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Judy has been married to Jeff for over 42 years. He is also a co-founder of Ji-Cheng Co. Ltd. Jeff is a member of the Rotary Club of Taipei Gardens. Together, they support The Rotary Foundation through the Judy and Jeff Endowed Rotary Peace Certificate Program Fellowship.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei Pei-An' ows_DistrictRI='3520' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JudyandJeffChang/Chang Jeff and Judy.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='800' ows_LinkTitle='FredShengTsaiWuandLiFongWuLee' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Fred Sheng-Tsai Wu and Li-Fong Lee' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Fred is a graduate of the National Taipei Institute of Technology in Taiwan. He is a deputy engineer for public transportation at Ke Chong Industry Co. Ltd., which specializes in the manufacture of vehicles including fire engines, medical buses, and maintenance vehicles. Fred enjoys participating in his community’s annual blood drive.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;A member of the Hsintien club since 1989, Fred was club president in 1995-96 and served as district governor in 2003-04. Fred’s proudest accomplishment during his tenure as governor was improving the Youth Exchange program application and selection process to make them more easily accessible and financially transparent.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Fred has been married to his wife, Li-Fong, for over 57 years. She is the executive director of Ke Chong Industry Co. Ltd. Her interests include calligraphy, singing, and traveling. The couple have four children, one of whom is a Rotarian.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Hsintien' ows_DistrictRI='3480' ows_RegionRI='Hsintien' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/FredShengTsaiWuandLiFongWuLee/Wu Fred Sheng-Tsai and Li-Fong Fu-Lee.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='801' ows_LinkTitle='WilliamChiuLienTsengandFengChuKao' ows_TitleDisplayRI='William Chiu-Lien Tseng and Feng-Chu Kao' ows_ClubNameRI='Pingtung East' ows_DistrictRI='3510' ows_RegionRI='Pingtung' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/WilliamChiuLienTsengandFengChuKao/Tseng William Chiu-Lien and Feng-Chu Kao.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='802' ows_LinkTitle='SamuelR.Whitfield' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Samuel R. Whitfield' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Immediately after graduating from the University of Georgia in 1952, Samuel Whitfield reported for duty in the U.S. Army. Three years later, after his army service, which included a stint in Korea, he settled in Smyrna, Georgia, where he worked as an agency manager for Prudential Insurance Company. Dissatisfied with local banking services, he helped found Security National Bank, and served as a director for 30 years; later, the bank became part of SunTrust Bank. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;An active participant in his local church, Sam became a deacon and served as church treasurer for 10 years. He was also chairman of the Smyrna Civil Service Board and served two terms as chairman of the Cobb County Board of Education.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sam became a charter member of the Rotary Club of Smyrna in 1963. He served as treasurer and president, as well as chair of the club Foundation committee. Sam has maintained perfect club attendance for 50 years and has attended at least 40 district assemblies. He enjoys participating in projects that support clean water, wheelchair access, and PolioPlus.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sam was married to his wife, Grace, for 42 years before she succumbed to cancer in 1993.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Smyrna' ows_DistrictRI='6900' ows_RegionRI='Georgia' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SamuelR.Whitfield/Whitfiled Sam.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='803' ows_LinkTitle='KathleenStillwellMyers' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Kathleen Stillwell Myers' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Kathleen Stillwell Myers received her bachelor of arts degree in English from Florida State University. A lifelong resident of Atlanta, Kathy had a successful career at AT&amp;amp;T. She was an active supporter of her local church, where she was a deacon, served on the business and finance committee, and was a member of the handbell choir. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Kathy joined the Rotary Club of North Fulton in 2008 and served as secretary for two consecutive years. Her favorite club project was working with Heart of Africa, which provides food, water, clothing, health care, and educational opportunities to children in Swaziland. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;In 1988, Kathy married Howard G. Myers, whom she met on vacation while in North Carolina. They were married for four years before his passing in 1992. Kathy enjoyed traveling throughout Israel in her free time, to deepen her religious faith. She passed away in 2012, after a long battle with Cushing’s disease and cancer.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='North Fulton' ows_DistrictRI='6900' ows_RegionRI='Georgia' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/KathleenStillwellMyers/Myers Kathy.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='804' ows_LinkTitle='ArthurC.MillsIIIandJaneM.Mills' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Arthur C. Mills III and Jane M. Mills' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Arthur “Hap” Mills graduated from Hobart College in New York State with a bachelor of science degree in chemistry and mathematics. He then served in the U.S. Air Force for seven years. From 1964 to 1974, Hap was the owner and master rod builder at H.L. Leonard Rod Company, followed by two years as a consultant to small businesses. He then became a sales agent for MONY Securities Corporation, retiring in 1988.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Hap joined the Rotary Club of Monroe-Woodbury, New York, in 1981, and after moving to Florida, joined the India-Lucie club and later supervised the club’s merge with the Stuart club. He is currently a member of the Rotary Club of Hobe Sound/Port Salerno. During his years in Rotary, Hap has served in many club roles, including secretary, treasurer, and president, and is currently his club’s membership chair.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Jane Mills earned her bachelor of arts degree from William Smith College and her master’s degree from the State University of New York at Cortland. She worked as a classroom teacher for 23 years before retiring in 1988. She is currently active with her church and is a member of the Garden Club of Stuart. Jane joined the Rotary Club of Stuart in 2001 and served as president in 2003-04. She is currently a member of the Rotary Club of Stuart-Sunrise. Jane was her district’s RotaKids chair from 2001 to 2011. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Hap and Jane have been married for over 55 years. They have hosted six Rotary Youth Exchange students and are still in touch with most of them. Hap and Jane have eight children and four grandchildren.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Hobe Sound/Port Salerno, and the Rotary Club of Stuart-Sunrise' ows_DistrictRI='6930' ows_RegionRI='Florida' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/ArthurC.MillsIIIandJaneM.Mills/Mills Arthur and Jane.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='805' ows_LinkTitle='EmmanuelNuelandGoodyMark' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Emmanuel “Nuel” and Goody Mark' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Emmanuel Mark is an estate surveyor and valuer. He is the founder of Nuel Mark Group, whose subsidiaries are involved in commercial and residential real estate consulting and sustainable environmental strategies. Emmanuel is the past national publicity secretary of the Nigeria Institute of Estate Surveyors &amp;amp; Valuers. Also active in the community, he works to interest youths in entrepreneurship and to help women who wish to start their own businesses, and has donated relief materials to flood-affected communities through his Nuel Mark Foundation.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Emmanuel was a member of both Interact and Rotaract. He joined the Rotary Club of Port Harcourt Central in 2004 and has served as president. He also has been the chair of the district Rotaract committee. His favorite club projects include providing instructional materials to local schools, providing water and bore hole facilities in Harcourt, and supporting PolioPlus.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Emmanuel has been married to his wife, Goody, for over six years and they have one child. Goody works in the wholesale/retail industry, is the chair of her church, and has worked alongside Emmanuel to help more than two dozen women with start-up businesses. Emmanuel and Goody support The Rotary Foundation through the Sir Emmanuel and Lady Goody Mark Endowment Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Port Harcourt Central' ows_DistrictRI='9140' ows_RegionRI='Rivers State' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/EmmanuelNuelandGoodyMark/Mark Emmanuel.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Nigeria' ows_CountryCodeRI='NG' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='806' ows_LinkTitle='JohnW.andBrendaB.Kessler' ows_TitleDisplayRI='John W. and Brenda B. Kessler' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;John W. Kessler earned his bachelor of arts degree at the University of Southern California and then served in the U.S. Air Force. He began his career in 1966, founding Kessler Mfg. &amp;amp; Imports, a merchandise distribution company. John has been a member of the Freemasons, a community service organization, for over 45 years.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;John joined the Rotary Club of Wilmette in 1982 and became a founding member of the Rotary Club of Wilmette Harbor in 1990. He is a firm believer in the good works of Rotary, and his most satisfying Rotary activity is finding new members who want to make a difference. John and his wife, Brenda, also enjoy attending Rotary’s annual international conventions.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;John and Brenda have been married for over 40 years. Brenda is a retired teacher and accountant and was an active member of the Woman’s Club of Wilmette. Owing to John’s line of work, he and Brenda travel extensively all over the world. They have three children and three grandchildren.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Wilmette Harbor' ows_DistrictRI='6440' ows_RegionRI='Illinois' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JohnW.andBrendaB.Kessler/Kessler John and Brenda.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='807' ows_LinkTitle='AnnHendersonJohnsonandLamarJohnson' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Ann Henderson Johnson and Lamar Johnson' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Ann Henderson Johnson started working as a secretary at Aflac and eventually became one of three women simultaneously named the insurance company’s first female vice presidents. Ann was president of the Columbus, Georgia, chapter of the American Business Women’s Association, and served as the Georgia district governor of Toastmasters International. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;In 1991, Ann became a charter member of the Rotary Club of Muscogee-Columbus. She was the club’s fifth president, and in 1998 became the first female district governor in the state of Georgia. Ann became a member of the Rotary Club of Columbus in 2005 and remained a member until her passing in 2008.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Lamar Johnson began his career as an investigator in the U.S. Department of Labor and was promoted to deputy administrator in the department’s Wage and Hour Division. He also worked as a labor law consultant and federal investigator and has had 40 years of service with the Navy, Army, and Coast Guard. Lamar joined the Rotary Club of North Fulton in 2001 before joining the Rotary Club of Columbus in 2005. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Ann and Lamar married in 2005 after 50 years of friendship. Ann is survived by her two sons, four grandchildren, and one great-grandchild. Lamar has six children and five grandchildren. He continues Ann’s legacy of community service&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Columbus' ows_DistrictRI='6900' ows_RegionRI='Georgia' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/AnnHendersonJohnsonandLamarJohnson/Johnson Lamar and Anne.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='808' ows_LinkTitle='KennethW.andRuthE.Grabeau' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Kenneth W. and Ruth E. Grabeau' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Kenneth W. Grabeau is founder, president, and CEO of Monarch Instrument, an electronics manufacturing company. He has served on and chaired the boards of United Way of Greater Nashua, Girls Inc., and Pure Water for the World.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Ken joined the Rotary Club of Nashua West in 1978. He served as its president in 1983-84 and as district governor in 1997-98. A Rotary International director from 2010 to 2012, Ken has held many Rotary positions. During his term as director, he was chair of the Programs Committee and Rotarian Action Groups Committee, and served as special adviser to the Executive Committee. He currently is a member of the Election Review and Council on Legislation Review committees. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;PolioPlus is one of Ken’s favorite Rotary projects. In 2003 and 2005, he traveled to Cameroun and Ghana to participate in National Immunization Days, an experience that had a lasting, inspiring effect on him. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Ken and his wife, Ruth, have been married for 46 years. An active Rotary spouse, Ruth enjoys participating with Ken in Rotary activities and events, including the polio immunization trips. She also enjoys practicing tai chi and scrapbooking. Ken and Ruth have two children and four grandchildren. They support Rotary through the Kenneth and Ruth Grabeau Endowed Rotary Peace Centers Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Nashua West' ows_DistrictRI='7870' ows_RegionRI='New Hampshire' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/KennethW.andRuthE.Grabeau/Grabeau Kenneth and Ruth1.jpg' ows_Image2PathRI='Donors/KennethW.andRuthE.Grabeau/grabeau1.jpg' ows_Image3PathRI='Donors/KennethW.andRuthE.Grabeau/Grabeau2.jpg' ows_Image4PathRI='Donors/KennethW.andRuthE.Grabeau/grabeau3.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='809' ows_LinkTitle='OlorogunBarr.KennethO.Gbagi' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Olorogun Barr. Kenneth O. Gbagi' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Kenneth Gbagi holds a degree in both law and criminology and works as a legal practitioner and criminologist. His law firm, Kenneth Gbagi &amp;amp; Associates, has four offices in Nigeria, and he is the youngest person to serve as chairman of the Legal Aid Council of Nigeria. Active in his political party, Kenneth is the former minister of state for education. He is also the chairman of The Gbagi Foundation, which provides education and jobs to those in need.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Kenneth joined the Rotary Club of Ikeja South in 1987 and is a charter member of the Osubi club, of which he has been vice president. Kenneth is passionate about Rotary projects that help those living in impoverished situations, and about polio eradication efforts, especially in Africa. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Kenneth supports The Rotary Foundation through the Kenneth Gbagi Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Osubi' ows_DistrictRI='9140' ows_RegionRI='Delta State' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/OlorogunBarr.KennethO.Gbagi/Gbagi Kenneth.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Nigeria' ows_CountryCodeRI='NG' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='810' ows_LinkTitle='RichardBartonandJaneHopson1' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Richard Barton and Jane Hopson' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Rich Barton, the son of a sheet-metal worker, was raised in a working-class home and was the first person in his family to attend college. After earning a civil engineering degree from the University of Illinois in 1964, he took a job with the American Bridge division of U.S. Steel. Later, he would work as a construction engineer on some of the world’s most prominent buildings, including the John Hancock Center in Chicago and the World Trade Center in New York City, as well as numerous roads and bridges. During his career, he has owned a construction company and a hotel, and currently owns RB Property Investments, a property holding company.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Rich became a Rotarian in 1995 as a member of the Rotary Club of Burr Ridge, and he quickly gained a reputation for spirited involvement in the club’s projects. He later joined the Rotary Club of Hinsdale. He is a past president of both clubs.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Rich and Jane are strong supporters of The Rotary Foundation and set up a charitable remainder trust to fund multiple projects.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Hinsdale' ows_DistrictRI='6450' ows_RegionRI='Illinois' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/RichardBartonandJaneHopson1/Barton Richard and Jane Hopson.jpg' ows_Image2PathRI='Donors/RichardBartonandJaneHopson1/Barton1.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Chair Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='811' ows_LinkTitle='MichaelandMisiOmotosho' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Michael and Misi Omotosho' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Michael Omotosho holds undergraduate degrees from both Kwara State Polytechnic and Ahmadu Bello University. He has a graduate degree in management from the University of Lagos, attended the High Potential Leadership Program of Harvard Business School, and received his doctorate in business administration from Commonwealth University. He is currently working on a doctorate in professional ethics from Trinity College. Mike works in the field of health care and has managed nonprofits from the ground up. He is also active in his local Toastmasters club and has served as a trustee and board member of the Abuja Philharmonic Orchestra.
&lt;br&gt;Mike joined the Rotary Club of Gbagada in 2004, serving as club secretary and president before joining the Abuja Metro club in 2010. Mike has served as chair of the district public relations committee and the district Permanent Fund subcommittee. Mike will also become a district governor in 2015-16. Rotary’s RYLA program is a favorite of his, and he has coordinated the annual RYLA programs for districts 9110 and 9125 for the past nine years. 
&lt;br&gt;Mike and his wife, Misi, have been married for over 13 years and have three children. A human resources consultant, Misi served two terms as president of the Inner Wheel Club of Gbagada and also supports projects that aid physically challenged children and that promote the training and recruitment of unemployed domestic workers.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Abuja Metro' ows_DistrictRI='9125' ows_RegionRI='Federal Capital Territory' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/MichaelandMisiOmotosho/Omotosho Mike and Misi.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Nigeria' ows_CountryCodeRI='NG' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='812' ows_LinkTitle='MichaelOlayiwolaandAdebolaOlawaleCole' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Michael and Adebola Olawale-Cole' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Michael Olawale-Cole is an alumnus of the University of Lagos, South West London College, and All Saint’s University. He is a former assistant chief accountant at Lever Brothers Ltd. and owns a group of businesses that focus on insurance brokering, tourism, management consulting, and oil production. He has served as the president and chairman of the Nigerian Council of Registered Insurance Brokers and is currently the treasurer of the Lagos Chamber of Commerce and Industry, as well as president and chairman of the Nigerian Institute of Management.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Michael joined the Rotary Club of Isolo in 1980 and has served as secretary and president. During his term as district governor in 2005-06, he led efforts to build a Rotary center in Lagos and helped start work on over 80 bore holes to provide water to residents. Michael received a Presidential Citation and Rotary’s Service Above Self Award.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Michael has been married to Adebola for over 36 years; they have four children and two grandchildren. Adebola works in business management and enjoys volunteering with her church. She is the past president of her Inner Wheel club and has attended close to 20 Rotary International conventions with Michael. Together, Michael and Adebola support The Rotary Foundation through the Chief Michael Olawale-Cole Endowed Fund for Rotary Peace Centers.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Isolo' ows_DistrictRI='9110' ows_RegionRI='Lagos State' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/MichaelOlayiwolaandAdebolaOlawaleCole/Olawale-Cole Michael.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Nigeria' ows_CountryCodeRI='NG' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='813' ows_LinkTitle='AdebisiClementiandWinnieAdegoke' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Adebisi Clementi and Winnie Adegoke' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Adebisi Clementi holds a bachelor’s degree in cultural anthropology. A farmer and entrepreneur, Bisi is a pioneering researcher in agricultural industries; his breakthroughs include ways to cut poultry feeding costs, the first floating fish feed, and a dam/pond construction technique that does not require the use of electricity. Bisi is also involved in his local community, providing two undergraduate scholarships annually, facilitating regular construction of bore holes for potable water, and volunteering at the School for the Handicapped in Osogbo.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Bisi has been a member of the Rotary Club of Osogbo since 2001. He has served as club president and as assistant governor. Among the club projects he enjoys most are the adult literacy program, the water and sanitation bore holes project, and the HIV/AIDS campaign. Bisi is also a strong supporter of the PolioPlus program. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Bisi is married to Winnie Adegoke, who is also a farmer and a member of the local Inner Wheel club. Bisi and Winnie have two children.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Osogbo' ows_DistrictRI='9125' ows_RegionRI='Osun State' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/AdebisiClementiandWinnieAdegoke/Adegoke Adebisi.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Nigeria' ows_CountryCodeRI='NG' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='814' ows_LinkTitle='EdFuta' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Ed Futa' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Ed Futa served as general secretary and chief operating officer of Rotary International and The Rotary Foundation from 2000 until his retirement in 2011. He managed operations for one of the world’s largest global humanitarian service organizations with 33,000 Rotary clubs in nearly every country in the world.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;As general secretary, Ed oversaw a diverse staff of more than 650 at Rotary’s World Headquarters in Evanston, Illinois, USA, and in seven international offices. He was a champion for staff, creating an atmosphere that fostered growth and professional development, which enabled them to provide superior support to clubs around the world. He also focused staff efforts on Rotary’s top priority, the global eradication of polio. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Before joining the Rotary staff in 1999 as associate general secretary, Ed was president of an international marketing consulting firm, in his home state of Hawaii. He has served on the Board of Governors of the YMCA and as a mediator in the Neighborhood Justice Center of Honolulu.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;A Rotarian since 1979, Ed was governor of District 5000 in 1988-89. He supports the Rotary Peace Centers.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='East Honolulu' ows_DistrictRI='5000' ows_RegionRI='Hawaii' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/EdFuta/Futa Ed.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='815' ows_LinkTitle='ShuheiandTamakiHotta' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Shuhei and Tamaki Hotta' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Shuhei Hotta is a graduate of Kinki University in Japan, where he earned a bachelor’s degree in applied chemistry. He began working at Osaka Yuka Industries Ltd., a chemicals company, in 1972 and has been serving as CEO since 1992. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Shuhei has been a member of the Hirakata club, of which his late father was also a member, since 2009. Committed to serving the world through vocational service, Shuhei enjoys helping with child literacy programs as well as participating in clean water projects. He believes that providing access to safe water and food to those in need will eventually eliminate many infectious diseases that claim so many lives.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Shuhei has been married to Tamaki for more than 35 years and they have two children and one grandchild. Tamaki enjoys winter sporting activities, including figure skating and skiing. Shuhei and Tamaki support The Rotary Foundation through the Shuhei Hotta Rotary Peace Centers Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Hirakata' ows_DistrictRI='2660' ows_RegionRI='Osaka' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/ShuheiandTamakiHotta/Hotta Shuhei.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Japan' ows_CountryCodeRI='JP' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='816' ows_LinkTitle='ShojiAkutsu' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Shoji Akutsu' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Shoji Akutsu graduated from Meiji University in Japan with a bachelor’s degree in commerce. He co-founded Texcel Co. Ltd., a distributor of advanced semiconductors, and was its president and CEO from 1975 to 2004. Shoji also founded Technology and Communications Inc., an analog integrated-circuit design and consulting company. He also served on the board of directors of O2 Micro International and had been the vice chair of the Distributors Association of Foreign Semiconductors from 1991 to 2004. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Shoji joined the Rotary Club of Tokyo Shinagawa Chuo in 1980. He was club president in 2000-01, assistant district governor in 2007-08, and assistant regional Rotary Foundation coordinator in 2011-13. Recognizing that young people are our future, he enjoys working on projects that encourage youth development.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Shoji was married to Yuri for 18 years before she passed away. They have one daughter. Shoji and Yuri chose to support The Rotary Foundation through the Shoji Akutsu Endowed Global Grant, which supports scholars studying peace and conflict prevention and resolution.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Tokyo Shinagawa Chuo' ows_DistrictRI='2750' ows_RegionRI='Tokyo' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/ShojiAkutsu/Akutsu Shoji.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Japan' ows_CountryCodeRI='JP' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='817' ows_LinkTitle='KenjuandKyokoTakekoshi' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Kenju and Kyoko Takekoshi' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Kenju Takekoshi is a professional in the high-pressure gas production and supply business. He has been the CEO, president, and chair of several corporations, including Sankoh Sansho Corporation, Kyodo High-Pressure Gas Industry Corporation, Sankoh Medical Corporation, and TCB Corporation.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Kenju joined the Rotary Club of Gifu South in 1975. He was president in 1991-92 and became district governor in 2004-05. Kenju was an assistant regional Rotary Foundation coordinator from 2009-2011 and was appointed as an endowment/major gift adviser for 2013-14. He enjoys his work on Rotary grant projects because it allows him to use his knowledge and skills to enhance the lives of the less fortunate. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Kenju had been married to his wife, Kyoko, for 50 years before her passing in 2012. Kyoko was appointed a local welfare commissioner by the Japanese government, a position of honor that she enjoyed immensely. Kenju and Kyoko have one son, one daughter, and two grandchildren. They have two endowed funds, which support The Rotary Foundation’s SHARE system and the Rotary Peace Centers program.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Gifu South' ows_DistrictRI='2630' ows_RegionRI='Gifu' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/KenjuandKyokoTakekoshi/Takekoshi Kenju.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Japan' ows_CountryCodeRI='JP' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='818' ows_LinkTitle='ToyoakiandNaomiFujibayashi' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Toyoaki and Naomi Fujibayashi' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Toyoaki Fujibayashi holds a bachelor’s degree from Hosei University. Upon graduation, he became the CEO of Nakatsu Reitou Co., Ltd. Over the years he has administered businesses in cold storage warehousing. He owns three companies and is the CEO of Myoukou Kigyou Co., Ltd. He supports the same children’s nursing home in Nagasaki that his father supported and for over 30 years has been a sponsor of the foster parent program of the Christian Child Welfare Association.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Toyoaki has been a member of the Yokohama Tsurumi North club since 1979. He has served as club president (1992-93), district governor (2004-05), RRIMC (2008-10). His favorite Rotary activities include his club’s drug abuse prevention campaign, the Japan Yoneyama scholarship program, and events with the local Interactors.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Toyoaki and his wife, Naomi, have been married for over 40 years. She works as a company executive. She is incredibly supportive of Toyoaki’s Rotary career and has volunteered at blood drives and environmental cleanup activities and has attended Rotary International conventions. Also, the couple has served as SAA for International Assembly and International conventions.&amp;nbsp; Toyoaki and Naomi have two children and one grandchild. The couple supports The Rotary Foundation through the Toyoaki and Naomi Fujibayashi Endowed Fund and the Toyoaki Fujibayashi Endowed Fund for the Rotary Peace Centers.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Yokohama Tsurumi North' ows_DistrictRI='2590' ows_RegionRI='Kanagawa' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/ToyoakiandNaomiFujibayashi/Fujibayashi Toyoaki.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Japan' ows_CountryCodeRI='JP' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='819' ows_LinkTitle='SeijiandNobukoKita' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Seiji and Nobuko Kita' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Seiji Kita has been the CEO of Shinkenkogyo Co. Ltd., a construction company, since the 1970s. He is a permanent board member of the Saitama City Construction Association, and helped draft its code of ethics. An active volunteer in his community, Seiji has served as the vice chair for both the Saitama Prefecture Sports Association and the Saitama City Sports Association. He has also served as the chair of the Saitama Prefecture High School PTA Foundation.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Seiji has been a member of the Rotary Club of Urawa East since 1982. Having served as club president (1999-2000), district governor (2004-05), and regional Rotary Foundation coordinator (2007-10), he will serve as a 2013-15 Rotary International director. A longtime supporter of the Foundation’s Ambassadorial Scholars program, Seiji also supports the Rotary Peace Centers program.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Seiji has been married to Nobuko for more than 45 years and they have three sons and five grandchildren. Nobuko has been an avid supporter of Seiji’s Rotary career, especially during his year as district governor. They support The Rotary Foundation through the Seiji Kita Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Urawa East' ows_DistrictRI='2770' ows_RegionRI='Saitama' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SeijiandNobukoKita/Kita Seiji.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Japan' ows_CountryCodeRI='JP' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='820' ows_LinkTitle='KazuhikoOzawa' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Kazuhiko Ozawa' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Kazuhiko Ozawa, a graduate of Gakushuin University in Japan, is in the hotel and restaurant management business and is currently the owner and president of Kamakura Park Hotel. He is president of the Yokosuka Chamber of Commerce, a former member of the Kanagawa Prefecture Public Safety Commission, and chair of the Yokosuka Arts Foundation.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Kaz has served in several Rotary leadership positions since he joined the Rotary Club of Yokosuka in 1978: club president (1994-95), district governor (2000-01), Rotary International director (2007-09), and Rotary Foundation Trustee (2010-14). He has served on several committees, including the Endowment Fund Committee for Japan; PolioPlus National Advocacy Advisors; and the 2010 Montréal, 2014 Sydney, and 2015 São Paulo convention committees, in addition to serving as a president’s representative in 2010-11.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Kaz is committed to supporting disaster recovery projects because he recognizes that the Foundation organizes projects to meet the needs of devastated communities in a timely manner. He also supports The Rotary Foundation through the Kazuhiko Ozawa Endowed Fund and the Kazuhiko Ozawa Rotary Peace Centers Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Yokosuka' ows_DistrictRI='2780' ows_RegionRI='Kanagawa' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/KazuhikoOzawa/Ozawa Kazuhiko.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Japan' ows_CountryCodeRI='JP' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='821' ows_LinkTitle='GlenA.andSharonA.Thomet' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Glen A. and Sharon A. Thomet' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Glen Thomet earned bachelor’s and master’s degrees in physical education at the University of Michigan in Ann Arbor, Michigan, USA. He taught elementary and junior high school physical education in Ann Arbor and also operated two fabric franchise stores with his wife, Sharon. After moving to Eugene, Oregon, Glen operated several retail businesses, including two bookstores, a men’s clothing store, and an ice cream parlor. He has served as the board chairman for his local theater and president of the University of Oregon’s athletic program booster club.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Glen became a member of the Rotary Club of Eugene Southtowne in 1982 and served as president from 1989 to 1990. After retiring and moving to Klamath Falls, he joined the Klamath County club. A polio survivor, Glen is an active supporter of PolioPlus and has traveled to Ethiopia to help administer the polio vaccine to children — an experience that he describes as one of the defining moments in his life.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Glen and Sharon have been married for over 54 years and have three children and three grandchildren. A retired nurse, Sharon has participated in events with P.E.O., an international women’s organization focused on education, and Assistance League, a community-based volunteer organization. She has actively supported Glen’s Rotary career, helping with local projects and attending district and international conferences with him. Glen and Sharon support The Rotary Foundation through the Glen A. and Sharon Thomet Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Klamath County' ows_DistrictRI='5110' ows_RegionRI='Oregon' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/GlenA.andSharonA.Thomet/Thomet Glen.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='GlenA.andSharonA.Thomet/GlenAndSharonThomets.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='822' ows_LinkTitle='JohnE.Stewart' ows_TitleDisplayRI='John E. Stewart' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;John E. Stewart graduated from North Carolina State University with a bachelor’s degree in nuclear engineering in 1954 and earned a master’s degree in business administration at the University of California, Los Angeles. He has worked as a registered professional engineer in 10 states, was part of a team that launched the first satellite powered by a nuclear reactor, has written more than 140 technical reports, and acted as a United States delegate to the International Atomic Energy Agency, which is part of the United Nations, to publish radioactivity standards. John is licensed to fly noncommercial planes, and also grows Christmas trees in his spare time.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;John was a member of Rotary clubs in Clayton, Missouri, and Canoga Park, California, before becoming a charter member of the Clemmons club in 1992 and serving as its second president. In 2009, he volunteered with Saving Little Hearts of Nicaragua, presenting gifts to children undergoing open-heart surgery. He received his Rotary club’s Avenues of Service Citation award in 2010.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;John and his partner, Carol Faber, a retired teacher, have been together for 17 years. Carol is an active supporter of John’s Rotary career and has traveled with him to service projects and international conventions. John has one son and three grandsons. He supports The Rotary Foundation through the John E. Stewart Endowment for the Rotary Peace Centers and the John Stewart Term Rotary Peace Fellowship.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Clemmons' ows_DistrictRI='7690' ows_RegionRI='North Carolina' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JohnE.Stewart/Stewart John.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='JohnE.Stewart/JohnStewart.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='823' ows_LinkTitle='YaleandBarbaraJones' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Yale and Barbara Jones' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Yale Jones received his undergraduate degree from Stanford University and his law degree from the University of California, Los Angeles. After his admission to the California Bar in 1966, he spent two years serving in the Peace Corps in Kenya. When he returned to California, he helped found the Jones, Clifford, Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson law practice in San Francisco, and he specialized in workers’ compensation law. An active volunteer, Yale served in several positions, for over 10 years, with the Nepal Youth Foundation, and for the past two years, he has been a Big Brother to an 11-year-old boy through Big Brothers Big Sisters of Northern New Mexico.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Yale joined the Taos-Milagro club in 2006 and was president in 2009-10. He has served as 2012-13 chair of the District 5520 Group Study Exchange Subcommittee and will be the 2013-14 chair of the district vocational training team subcommittee. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Yale and his wife, Barbara, have been married for over 17 years. Barbara has a doctorate in transpersonal psychology and works as a life coach specializing in personal fulfillment. In 2004, she founded the Nepal Youth Foundation’s Ankur Counseling Center, which provides support to children in need. Barbara is an enthusiastic supporter of Yale’s Rotary involvement and the couple enjoys attending RI conventions together.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taos-Milagro' ows_DistrictRI='5520' ows_RegionRI='New Mexico' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/YaleandBarbaraJones/JonesYale.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Foundation Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='824' ows_LinkTitle='ElizabethandHerbertHezlepIII' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Elizabeth and Herbert Hezlep III' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Herbert Hezlep has a bachelor’s degree in business administration from the University of California, Berkeley. In 1950, he joined his father’s small hardware manufacturing company, Acme General Corporation, which eventually was expanded from its base in Monrovia, California, to Canada and Europe. Herb served as executive vice president, president, and chairman of the board before retiring in 1988. Active in his community, he has served as president and board member of the YMCA of Monrovia and board member of Huntington Medical Research Institutes in Pasadena.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Herb followed in his father’s footsteps, joining the Rotary Club of Monrovia in 1958. He became club president in 1964-65, district Group Study Exchange chair in 1967-68, and district conference chair in 1973. Herb has been an active supporter of the Group Study Exchange program over the years and considers it his favorite Rotary Foundation program.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Herb and Elizabeth have been married for over 57 years. They have four children, four grandchildren, and one great-grandson. Liz is a retired society editor for the local newspaper and remains active with the Luminaires, a support group for the Doheny Eye Institute. Herb and Liz support The Rotary Foundation through the Herb Hezlep Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Monrovia' ows_DistrictRI='5300' ows_RegionRI='California' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/ElizabethandHerbertHezlepIII/Hezlep Herbert.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Foundation Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='825' ows_LinkTitle='JamesF.andSusanM.Hunt' ows_TitleDisplayRI='James F. and Susan M. Hunt' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;James Hunt earned a bachelor’s degree from The Ohio State University and a master’s degree from Baldwin-Wallace University. He was the president and CEO of The Brickyard, a wholesale brick distributor with several Ohio locations. Although he retired in February 2013, Jim continues to work as an adjunct instructor at the local community college, and he served as a director of the Northern Savings and Loan Company. Jim joined the Rotary Club of Elyria in 1979. He served as club president (1989-90), district governor (2001-02), and district Permanent Fund subcommittee chair (2002-05). He also was a leader of a Group Study Exchange team to the Philippines.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Susan Hunt has a bachelor’s degree in education from The Ohio State University. She worked as a business executive before retiring in 2006. An active community volunteer, Sue has participated in the Big Brothers Big Sisters program and was the president of Main Street Vermilion, a community preservation program. Sue is a third-generation Rotarian. She was a charter member of the Rotary Club of Elyria Sunrise in 1996 and served as its president in 1998-99. She has been a member of the Rotary Club of Vermilion since 2007, serving as club secretary from 2009 to 2012. In 2003, she led a Group Study Exchange team to Brazil. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;James and Susan have been married for over 44 years. They have two children, one of whom is a fourth-generation Rotarian, and one grandchild.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Elyria, Ohio, USA and Rotary Club of Vermillion' ows_DistrictRI='6600' ows_RegionRI='Ohio' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JamesF.andSusanM.Hunt/Hunt James.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='JamesF.andSusanM.Hunt/JamesAndSusanHunt.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='826' ows_LinkTitle='JonB.andLindaGrant' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Jon B. and Linda Grant' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Jon Grant earned his doctor’s degree in dental surgery from the University of Nebraska in 1968. He has received a Mastership Award from the Academy of General Dentistry and is a fellow of the American College of Dentists. Jon is a charter member and past president of the Rotary Club of Foster City. He has served as district governor (1994-95), regional Rotary Foundation coordinator (1998-2000), district permanent fund subcommittee chair (2005-08), and district Rotary Foundation chair (2011-12).&amp;nbsp; Jon has received several Rotary awards, including The Rotary Foundation Citation for Meritorious Service (1993) and Distinguished Service Award (1996), Service Above Self Award (1999), and the Avenues of Service Citation (2000). In 1985, Jon volunteered his dentistry services in a Vietnamese refugee camp located in the Philippines for five weeks through the Rotary Foundation’s 3-H program. Jon has traveled to over 40 countries to deliver wheelchairs on behalf of the Wheelchair Foundation. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Linda Grant worked as an international health care recruiter for Hospital Corporation International. Frequent business trips to Saudi Arabia helped ignite her passion for travel: She has visited more than 100 countries and all seven continents. Linda joined the Rotary Club of Foster City in 2001. She served as its president (2009-10) and club Foundation chair (2010-11). Linda works with her husband to coordinate contributions for the Wheelchair Foundation, which has distributed over 350,000 wheelchairs worldwide to people with disabilities who are unable to afford them.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Foster City' ows_DistrictRI='5150' ows_RegionRI='California' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JonB.andLindaGrant/Grant Jon.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='JonB.andLindaGrant/JonAndLindaGrant.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='827' ows_LinkTitle='HarleyandMaryJordan' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Harley and Mary Jordan' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Harley Jordan dropped out of high school to join the U.S. Coast Guard and served for five years. After taking a high school equivalency exam, he earned a bachelor’s degree in physics from the University of Denver. Then, as a civilian physicist for the U.S. Navy in Washington, D.C., he was able to attend George Washington University at night, earning his master’s in philosophy and doctorate in mathematical studies. Harley worked in the Department of Defense’s Office of the Chief of Operations as an operations research analyst and, after retiring from federal service in 1979, taught mathematics at Norwich University in Northfield, Vermont. He retired in 1988.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Harley joined the Rotary Club of Northfield in 1980 and twice served as club president before transferring to the Rotary Club of Central Vermont (Berlin-East Montpelier). He served as district governor (1990-91), club president (2005-06), district annual fund subcommittee chair (2003-06), and club Foundation chair (2011-12). Harley received The Rotary Foundation’s Citation for Meritorious Service in 1993.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Harley and his wife, Mary, had been married for 48 years before her passing in 2004. Mary was a legal secretary and enjoyed assisting Harley with his Rotary responsibilities.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Central Vermont (Berlin-East Montpelier)' ows_DistrictRI='7850' ows_RegionRI='Vermont' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/HarleyandMaryJordan/Jordan Harley and Mary.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='828' ows_LinkTitle='EngRungE.R.TsaiandSharonMeiShuiTsaiTseng' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Eng-Rung “E.R.” Tsai and Sharon Mei-Shui Tsai Tseng' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;E.R. Tsai is an expert in food and beverage service management. He helps plan, develop, and manage hotel properties and provides refrigerated and frozen warehouse services. E.R. is also a philanthropist andfounded the Want Taiwan Cultural Environment Foundation, which is dedicated to enhancing Taiwanese culture through environmental protection and cultural restoration. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;A member and former president (1996-97) of the Rotary Club of Taipei Jen-Ai, E.R. has been a special consultant to the governors of District 3520 since 2005. E.R. finds inspiration in all that Rotary has done for the End Polio Now campaign.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;E.R. has been married for over 37 years to Mei-Shui Tsai Tseng, who works in business and financial management. They have three children, two of whom are Rotarians.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei Jen-Ai' ows_DistrictRI='3520' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/EngRungE.R.TsaiandSharonMeiShuiTsaiTseng/Tsai Eng-Rung.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='829' ows_LinkTitle='SweetmeShuiMayChouandChuChenLin' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Sweetme Shui-May Chou and Chu-Chen Lin' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Sweetme Shui-May Chou was born in Taipei, Taiwan, and has spent her professional career working in the hotel management and real estate management industry. She founded several construction companies, including SweetMe Construction and Wi-Yang Construction. Sweetme also opened the SweetMe Hotspring Spa Resort in 2002. She is currently the chairperson of the Taipei Business District and Industrial Confederation. She also is the executive director of the National Hospitality Manager Association and a director of both the Real Estate Investment Association of Taipei and the Taipei Hotel Association.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sweetme joined the Rotary Club of Taipei Hwa Yueh in 2009, serving as club president in 2012-13. Her favorite club project as president was organizing the annual blood drive donation in which thousands of people participate. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sweetme has been married to Chu-Chen Lin for over 26 years. Chu-Chen works in the construction and engineering industry. He is an enthusiastic volunteer with the regional police club. Sweetme and Chu-Chen have two children. The couple supports The Rotary Foundation through the Chu-Chen Lin and Shui-May Chou Endowed Rotary Peace Certificate Program Fellowship.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei Hwa Yueh' ows_DistrictRI='3520' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SweetmeShuiMayChouandChuChenLin/Chou Sweetme Shui-May.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='830' ows_LinkTitle='HenryShunLiChangandCathyHsiangYuehLinChang' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Henry Shun-Li Chang and Cathy Hsiang-Yueh Chang Lin' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Henry Shun-Li Chang was born in Taichung, Taiwan. He studied architecture at the Chinese Culture University, and went on to obtain a graduate degree in business administration at Taiwan National University. Besides establishing development and construction companies, he has been the general manager of Rodex Fasteners Corp. since 1997, a company that manufactures stainless steel wires and screws. He is also a supervisor of Taiwan Industrial Fasteners Institute and a board director at SZU-I Industries Co. Ltd. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Henry joined the Rotary Club of Taipei Northeast in 1989. He has served as club president (2006-07), district secretary (2010-11), and district governor (2012-13). His favorite club project is New Generations Service, which helps children in need with after school care and meal programs.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Henry and his wife, Cathy Hsiang-Yueh Chang Lin, have been married for over 39 years. Cathy, a former employee at the Bank of Taiwan, has been retired since 1983. She volunteers at the National Taiwan University Hospital and the Liver Disease Prevention Foundation. Henry and Cathy have two children and four grandchildren. They support The Rotary Foundation through the Henry Shun-Li and Cathy Chang Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei Northeast' ows_DistrictRI='3520' ows_RegionRI='Taiwan' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/HenryShunLiChangandCathyHsiangYuehLinChang/Chang Henry Shun-Li.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='831' ows_LinkTitle='RicardoandJudyLynnhonoredbyNellieLin' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Ricardo and Judy Lynn, Honored by Nellie Lin' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Nellie Lin, born in Taipei, Taiwan, studied business administration at Hawaii Chaminade University. She is the president of Ricardo Lynn Furniture and Co. Her father, Ricardo Lynn, is a well-known Taiwanese Rotarian who inspired her to keep the family Rotary tradition alive. Nellie joined the Rotary Club of Taipei Ricardo, named after her father, in 2011. Some of her favorite projects were providing breakfast to low-income students, visiting disadvantaged children at the Bethesda Home for Challenged Children, and raising funds to aid victims of child prostitution in Cambodia.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Nellie has been married for 13 years to Shu-Hsun Chu, a cardiac surgeon. Nellie and Shu-Hsun support The Rotary Foundation through the Ricardo and Judy Lynn Endowed Fund for the Rotary Peace Centers, which is named for Nellie’s parents.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei East' ows_DistrictRI='3520' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/RicardoandJudyLynnhonoredbyNellieLin/Lin Nellie.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='832' ows_LinkTitle='NicholasC.KrayacichandJenniferE.Jones' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Nicholas C. Krayacich and Jennifer E. Jones' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Jennifer Jones is president and CEO of Media Street Productions Inc., a television production company in Windsor, Canada, that has won international awards for broadcasting excellence and has been named Company of the Year by the Windsor-Essex Regional Chamber of Commerce. Jennifer also serves as chair of the board of governors at the University of Windsor. Her spouse, Nicholas Krayacich, is a family physician who runs his own medical center in LaSalle, Ontario. He has served as president of the Essex County Medical Society and as a board member for Hearts Together for Haiti.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Jennifer became a Rotarian in 1996. Her Rotary leadership roles include president of the Rotary Club of Windsor-Roseland in 2001-02, governor of District 6400 in 2007-08, and district public relations chair from 2009-11. She has been honored for her professional and charitable efforts with a host of awards, including Rotary International’s Service Above Self Award, the YMCA Peace Medallion, and the Queen’s Diamond Jubilee Medal.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Nicholas became a Rotarian in 2001 and joined the Rotary Club of LaSalle-Centennial in 2010, assuming the role of club president in 2012-13. He and Jennifer are passionate about volunteer travel and have participated in missions to the Brazilian Amazon, Peru, Haiti, Venezuela, and Tanzania.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='LaSalle-Centennial, Ontario, Canada and Windsor-Roseland' ows_DistrictRI='6400' ows_RegionRI='Ontario' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/NicholasC.KrayacichandJenniferE.Jones/Krayacich Nicholas and Jennifer Jones.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='NicholasC.KrayacichandJenniferE.Jones/JenniferJonesAndNicholasKrayacich.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Canada' ows_CountryCodeRI='CA' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='833' ows_LinkTitle='RafaelM.GarciaIIIandMindaA.Garcia' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Rafael M. Garcia III and Minda A. Garcia' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Rafael “Raffy” Garcia III is the chairman and CEO of Mega Group of Computer Companies, a multinational conglomerate of 44 companies that specialize in high-technology systems. The company is based in the Philippines and has offices in the United States, Shanghai, Buenos Aires, Singapore, and Germany.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Raffy joined the Rotary Club of Pasig in 1971. He became club president in 2006-07 and during that year increased club membership by more than 50 percent, leading his club to receive several awards at the district level. Raffy received the Four Avenues of Service Award from Rotary International for his work on the Pasig Rotary GK Housing Village, which is a 159-unit housing project in Pasig City. Raffy served as district governor in 2011-12, during which he chartered three new Rotary clubs and increased membership districtwide. He is now spearheading the effort to build a Rotary center adjacent to the housing village, which will have a community center, a day-care and preschool center, a clinic, and offices for each of the 15 Rotary clubs in the Pasig area.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Raffy’s wife, Minda, volunteers for the Soroptimists, an organization that improves the lives of women and girls. She has served as the Soroptimists International Governor for the Philippines (2012-14). When not volunteering, Minda runs her own cut flower farm in Calamba, Laguna, and specializes in raising orchids, anthuriums, and palm trees. Raffy and Minda have four children and seven grandchildren.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Pasig' ows_DistrictRI='3800' ows_RegionRI='Rizal' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/RafaelM.GarciaIIIandMindaA.Garcia/Garcia III Rafael and Minda.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Philippines' ows_CountryCodeRI='PH' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Chair Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='834' ows_LinkTitle='LavernaDollimore' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Laverna Dollimore' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;The late Laverna Dollimore was born in Toronto. After high school, she studied business at Western Technical Commercial School and then worked as a secretary and bookkeeper. During World War II, Laverna served in the Women’s Royal Canadian Naval Service (Wrens) at HMCS Cornwallis in Halifax.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;After the war, Laverna returned to secretarial work in Toronto until joining Canada’s Department of External Affairs in 1956. She was posted to Canada’s embassies in Cairo, then Warsaw, Poland, and Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. She was sent to Leopoldville, Belgian Congo (present-day Kinshasa, Congo), in 1965, then, briefly, the Soviet Union (now Russia), Laos, and Cambodia. She was awarded the Canadian Peacekeeping Service Medal.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;In 1977, after six years in London, Laverna was assigned to the Canadian Embassy in Tehran, Iran. She helped six Americans who had evaded the 1979 hostage-taking at the U.S. Embassy there. While they were in hiding, she worked tirelessly to make them as comfortable as possible. She was awarded the Order of Canada for her role in their eventual rescue, known as the Canadian Caper. Her last post was Addis Ababa, Ethiopia. She retired in Brighton, Ontario, in 1983. Though not a Rotarian, Laverna admired The Rotary Foundation’s work in basic education and literacy and supported it through the Laverna Dollimore Fund. She passed away in 2011.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Trenton' ows_DistrictRI='7070' ows_RegionRI='Ontario' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/LavernaDollimore/Dollimore Laverna.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Canada' ows_CountryCodeRI='CA' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='835' ows_LinkTitle='BrynandRandyStyles' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Bryn and Randy Styles' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Bryn Styles was a member of the Canadian Armed Forces from 1971 to 1979. A pharmacist, Bryn received his bachelor of science degree from the University of Toronto. Bryn and his wife, Randy, who is also a pharmacist, have owned and operated two pharmacies, including an innovative practice that offers pain management, palliative care, and counseling on women’s health issues.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Bryn is a member of the Canadian Pharmacists Association and the Ontario Pharmacists’ Association. He has also volunteered as a chair of the Barrie YMCA, has served as director of the YMCA Canada, and is a member of the medical council for Gilda’s Club in Barrie. Bryn joined the Barrie-Huronia club in 1986. He has served Rotary as club president (1994-95), governor of District 7010 (2004-05), and regional Rotary Foundation coordinator (2010-12).
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Bryn and Randy have been married for over 39 years. Randy is a volunteer at Hospice Simcoe and enjoys playing the piano. She has actively supported Bryn’s Rotary career and frequently attended conferences, PETS, and conventions with him. The couple has two children and five grandchildren. Bryn and Randy support The Rotary Foundation through the Bryn and Randy Styles Rotary Peace Centers Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Barrie-Huronia' ows_DistrictRI='7010' ows_RegionRI='Ontario' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/BrynandRandyStyles/Styles Bryn and Randy.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='BrynandRandyStyles/BrynAndRandyStyles.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Canada' ows_CountryCodeRI='CA' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='836' ows_LinkTitle='WayneP.andBerniceChesley' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Wayne P. and Bernice Chesley' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Wayne Chesley was born in Punnichy, Saskatchewan, Canada. He started his career as a Ford dealer. After 16 years, he became a dealer for Toyota and remained with the company for 20 years before retiring in 2011. He is a past secretary and past president of the Medicine Hat Motor Dealer Association. He is also a past president of both the Pincher Creek Kinsman Club and the Pincher Creek Chamber of Commerce.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Wayne has been a member of the Rotary Club of Medicine Hat since 1998. He served as club president in 2008-09. His favorite Rotary club project is the annual Medicine Hat Rotary Music Festival, which his club has sponsored for more than 50 years. He has had the opportunity to travel to India with his wife, Bernice, to take part in a dedication ceremony for a Health, Hunger and Humanity club project. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Wayne and Bernice have been married for over 47 years. Bernie is a retired controller and an active volunteer in their community. She works with Girl Guides of Canada, Meals on Wheels, and children’s literacy programs. Wayne and Bernie have three children and one grandchild.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Medicine Hat' ows_DistrictRI='5360' ows_RegionRI='Alberta' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/WayneP.andBerniceChesley/Chesley Wayne and Bernice.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='WayneP.andBerniceChesley/WayneAndBerniceChesley.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Canada' ows_CountryCodeRI='CA' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='837' ows_LinkTitle='FloydA.andBettyLouLancia1' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Floyd A. and Betty Lou Lancia' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Floyd A. Lancia was born in Steubenville, Ohio. He received his undergraduate education at West Liberty State College and earned a master’s degree in education from the University of Massachusetts. From 1962 to 1977, he worked as an educator, serving as a music teacher, principal, and school superintendent. His current career is in real estate development and construction. Floyd serves on the Fort Wayne Building Department board of directors and has served as director, vice president, and president of the Fort Wayne Homebuilders Association.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Floyd joined the Rotary Club of Van Buren, Maine, in 1969 and was club president in 1974-75. In 1991, he joined the Rotary Club of Anthony Wayne (Fort Wayne) and has served as club president (2006-07), district governor (2009-10), and assistant regional Rotary Foundation coordinator (2010-13). He also has served as chair of district committees, including the membership development and nominating committees.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Floyd and his wife, Betty Lou, have been married for over 48 years. Betty Lou has a bachelor’s degree in music education from West Liberty State College and taught for 17 years before retiring in 1977. An avid singer, she sings with the Fort Wayne Philharmonic Chorus and directs a women’s choral group that entertains at nursing homes, offices, and community events. Floyd and Betty Lou have three children and six grandchildren.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Anthony Wayne (Fort Wayne)' ows_DistrictRI='6540' ows_RegionRI='Indiana' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/FloydA.andBettyLouLancia1/Lancia Floyd and Betty Lou.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='838' ows_LinkTitle='JohnandJaneMacKay' ows_TitleDisplayRI='John &quot;Sandy&quot; and Jane MacKay' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;John “Sandy” MacKay received his medical degree from the University of Saskatchewan in 1964. He became a certified specialist in ophthalmology in 1969 and practiced ophthalmology until his retirement in 2005. He is a past board director for the Alberta Medical Association and a past member of the Canadian Ophthalmology Society. Sandy is the chair of the Fifth Avenue United Church and the president of the Cypress Club Medicine Hat.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sandy, whose father was also a Rotarian, joined the Rotary Club of Medicine Hat in 1977. He has served as club president (1982-83) and governor of District 5360 (2002-03). He served as representative to the Council on Legislation in 2010. Sandy traveled to India in 2001 as a Discovery Grant recipient to work on a Health, Hunger and Humanity grant project for integrated village development.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sandy and his wife, Jane, have been married for over 48 years. Jane has a master of science and worked as a business manager. She enjoys pottery and serves as the education chair of Medalta, a ceramics museum. Jane also volunteers for the local community foundation and YMCA. Sandy and Jane have two children and four grandchildren.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Medicine Hat' ows_DistrictRI='5360' ows_RegionRI='Alberta' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JohnandJaneMacKay/MacKay John Sandy and Jane.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='JohnandJaneMacKay/SandyAndJaneMackay.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Canada' ows_CountryCodeRI='CA' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='839' ows_LinkTitle='ChrisandPennyOffer' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Chris and Penny Offer' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Chris Offer received a bachelor of arts degree in criminology from Simon Fraser University and a master’s in public administration from Carleton University. He worked for the Vancouver police force for over 25 years before retiring from the position of district commander in 1999. He is a recipient of the Canada Confederation Medal and Police Exemplary Service Medal. Chris has served as board director for the John Howard Society and the Vancouver AM Tourist Association. Chris, who joined the Rotary Club of Vancouver South in 1988, is a member of the Rotary Club of Ladner. Chris has served as club president (1991-92), district governor (1999-2000), and regional Rotary Foundation coordinator (2008-11).
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Penny Offer holds a master of social work from the University of Manitoba and a master’s degree in public administration from Carleton University. Among her many professional accomplishments, she has managed the social work department and established a brain injury program at the George Pearson Centre. Penny is also coauthor of the book Living with Brain Injury: A Guide for Families and Caregivers. In 2002, Penny joined the Rotary Club of Burnaby-Deer Lake, and later joined the Ladner club.&amp;nbsp; She has served as club president (2003-04) and district governor (2010-11). 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Chris and Penny support The Rotary Foundation through the Penny and Chris Offer Fund for Peace and Conflict Resolution.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Ladner' ows_DistrictRI='5040' ows_RegionRI='British Columbia' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/ChrisandPennyOffer/Offer Penny and Chris.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='ChrisandPennyOffer/ChrisAndPennyOffer.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Canada' ows_CountryCodeRI='CA' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='840' ows_LinkTitle='CecilPanchoPadilla' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Cecil “Pancho” Padilla' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Cecil “Pancho” Padilla was born in Orville, California, USA. He attended Sacramento State College where he studied administration and marketing. Pancho has spent most of his professional career with Pacific Gas and Electric (PG&amp;amp;E), starting as a temporary laborer in 1959 and moving up through several departments before retiring as a member of the senior management team. He continues to work with PG&amp;amp;E as a consultant with their retiree association.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Pancho joined Rotary in the 1970s as a member of the Placerville and Sacramento clubs. He joined the Rotary Club of Winters in 1978. He has served as club president (1982-83 and 1991-92) and club Rotary Foundation chair (2009-12). Pancho’s first Rotary trip to Baja, Mexico, is a defining moment in his Rotary experience; since working with locals in a small fishing village there to plan and build a dental clinic, he has gone on to travel to over 60 countries on medical missions, bridge building projects, and orphanage renovation programs on behalf of Rotary.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Pancho is an active volunteer in his community. He has served the Chamber of Commerce in various capacities and has been a city planning commissioner. He currently serves as a first responder for the Red Cross and volunteers for Habitat for Humanity and a local crisis center. Pancho has one son and two grandchildren.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Winters' ows_DistrictRI='5160' ows_RegionRI='California' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/CecilPanchoPadilla/Padilla Cecil.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='841' ows_LinkTitle='OswaldoandHisameTakata' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Oswaldo and Hisame Takata' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Oswaldo Takata is currently a construction company owner, but he has been a farmer, a produce seller, a truck driver, and a retailer. A member of the Rotary Club of São Paulo-Sudeste since 1984, he served as club president in 1993-94. Supporting PolioPlus and participating in community fundraising events hosted by his Rotary club are activities that Oswaldo finds particularly rewarding.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Oswaldo has been married to Hisame for over 42 years. She is a pediatrician who has been volunteering her medical assistance and providing free medicines to students at Escola Valentim Gentil for over 20 years. She is also the chair of Chama Social de Asistência ao Excepcional, an organization that provides assistance to people with special needs. Oswaldo and Hisame have one son, who is a Rotarian, and one grandson.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='São Paulo-Sudeste' ows_DistrictRI='4420' ows_RegionRI='São Paulo' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/OswaldoandHisameTakata/Takata Oswaldo and Hisame.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Brazil' ows_CountryCodeRI='BR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='842' ows_LinkTitle='TonyHungMingChangandJuliaTaiHuaChenChang' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Tony Hung-Ming Chang and Julia Tai-Hua Chen Chang' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Tony Hung-Ming Chang was born in Taiwan. He attended the National Tsing-Hua University, where he obtained a bachelor of science degree. He is the founder of Deuchem Co. Ltd. and was chairman for 30 years until his retirement in 2008. Deuchem is a leading supplier of special chemicals for the paint and coating industry.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Tony joined the Rotary Club of Hsinchu Northwest in 1995. He has held several positions within Rotary including club president (2000-01), district Annual Fund subcommittee chair (2009-10), and district governor (2011-12). During his year as governor, the district’s club performed more than 100 community services, a World Community Service medical team was sent to Nepal, and district Rotarians contributed record high donations to The Rotary Foundation.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Tony and his wife, Julia Tai-Hua Chen Chang, have been married for over 35 years. Since retiring in 2008, Julia has enjoyed focusing on her hobbies, which include singing and oil painting. They have two children and one grandchild. Tony and Julia support The Rotary Foundation through the Tony Hung-Ming Chang and Julia Tai-Hua Chen Chang Endowed Fund for the Rotary Peace Centers.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Hsinchu Northwest' ows_DistrictRI='3500' ows_RegionRI='Hsinchu' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/TonyHungMingChangandJuliaTaiHuaChenChang/Chang Tony Hung-Ming.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='843' ows_LinkTitle='SuryaandForamVarsani1' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Surya and Foram Varsani' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Surya became a Rotarian at the age of 24. He was a member of the Rotary Club of Golders Green, Greater London, England. He served as club president and assistant governor. Before his untimely death in July 2009 at the age of 39, Surya was a civil and structural engineer who enjoyed a variety of sports. In 2003, he ran the London Marathon. Foram Varsani holds a master’s degree in medical microbiology. She was a biomedical scientist, a senior biomedical scientist, and a clinical scientist before changing her professional focus to work as a director in her family’s construction business in Seychelles.&amp;nbsp; In November 2009, Foram became a Rotarian when she joined the Rotary Club of Victoria, Seychelles. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The couple lived in London after they were married in 1996, and they considered themselves a Rotary family because they involved their two young children in their Rotary activities. Together, Surya and Foram hosted Group Study Exchange teams and Ambassadorial Scholars. Her father-in-law, Past District Governor V.J. Patel, is a member of the same club, and he and his wife, Kusum, are also Arch C. Klumph Society members.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Victoria, Mahé and the Rotary Club of Golders Green' ows_DistrictRI='1130,9220' ows_RegionRI='London' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SuryaandForamVarsani1/Varsani Foram Surya.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='SuryaandForamVarsani1/ForamVarsani.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='United Kingdom' ows_CountryCodeRI='GB' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='844' ows_LinkTitle='SuryaandForamVarsani' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Foram and Surya Varsani' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Surya became a Rotarian at the age of 24. He was a member of the Rotary Club of Golders Green, Greater London, England. He served as club president and assistant governor. Before his untimely death in July 2009 at the age of 39, Surya was a civil and structural engineer who enjoyed a variety of sports. In 2003, he ran the London Marathon. Foram Varsani holds a master’s degree in medical microbiology. She was a biomedical scientist, a senior biomedical scientist, and a clinical scientist before changing her professional focus to work as a director in her family’s construction business in Seychelles.&amp;nbsp; In November 2009, Foram became a Rotarian when she joined the Rotary Club of Victoria, Seychelles. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The couple lived in London after they were married in 1996, and they considered themselves a Rotary family because they involved their two young children in their Rotary activities. Together, Surya and Foram hosted Group Study Exchange teams and Ambassadorial Scholars. Her father-in-law, Past District Governor V.J. Patel, is a member of the same club, and he and his wife, Kusum, are also Arch C. Klumph Society members.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Golders Green, London, England and the Rotary Club of Victoria' ows_DistrictRI='9220,1130' ows_RegionRI='Mahé' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SuryaandForamVarsani/Varsani Foram Surya.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='SuryaandForamVarsani/ForamVarsani.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Seychelles' ows_CountryCodeRI='SC' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='845' ows_LinkTitle='YoungKooParkandEunHwaChang' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Young Koo Park and Eun-Hwa Chang' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Young Koo Park is a graduate of the Hankuk University of Foreign Studies. An entrepreneur, he worked for Mitsui &amp;amp; Co. and Samyang Tire Co. before becoming the director of Kumho Electric Inc. in 1989. He is currently the chairman and CEO of Kumho Electric, which is the leading electric and lighting company in Korea. He also serves as vice chairman for the Korea Standard Association.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The son of a Rotarian, Young Koo joined the Rotary Club of Seoul Joongang in 1986. He served as club president in 2002-03; his club received the RI Presidential Citation award the same year. Young Koo served as district governor in 2010-11, and is a member of The Rotary Foundation’s Permanent Fund Committee for Korea. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Young Koo is married to Eun-Hwa Chang. Eun-Hwa is a graduate of the Ewha Womans University and studied Buddhism at Dongkuk University. She has an interest in graphic design and in her spare time enjoys reading. Young Koo and Eun-Hwa have two children. They support The Rotary Foundation through the Young Koo Park Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Seoul Joongang' ows_DistrictRI='3650' ows_RegionRI='Seoul' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/YoungKooParkandEunHwaChang/Park Young.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='YoungKooParkandEunHwaChang/YoungKooParkAndEunHwaChang.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='846' ows_LinkTitle='ByongSeolChoiandAJongLee' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Byong Seol Choi and A Jong Lee' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Byong Seol Choi, who attended the Seoul National University of Education and the College of Law at Kyung Hee University, is CEO of Daegeon BS Co. Ltd. and chairman of Kyunghan Industry Co. Ltd. He is a member of the National Unification Advisory Council, deputy chair of the Catholic Businessmen’s Association of Korea, and chairman of the Catholic Young Senior Academy.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Byong Seol joined the Rotary Club of Seoul-Seocho in 1992. He served as club president in 1997-98 and district governor in 2006-07 and 2011-12. He has been his district’s Rotary Foundation committee chair (2009-12) and chair of the Permanent Fund committee for Korea (2012-13). He is a recipient of the Service Above Self Award.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Byong Seol and A Jong Lee have been married for over 40 years and have three children and four grandchildren. A retired pharmacist, A Jong volunteers her time and expertise at the Joseph Clinic, a charitable health care facility. Byong Seol and A Jong support The Rotary Foundation through an endowed fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Seoul-Seocho' ows_DistrictRI='3640' ows_RegionRI='Seoul' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/ByongSeolChoiandAJongLee/Choi Byong.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='ByongSeolChoiandAJongLee/ByongSeolChoi.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='847' ows_LinkTitle='HiroshiandSumaI.Shimuta' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Hiroshi and Suma I. Shimuta' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Hiroshi Shimuta studied economy, law, and business administration while attending university. He spent much of his professional life working in Brazil’s financial markets. He is currently the owner of Nicon, a construction materials company. Hiroshi also runs the Escola Profissionalizante de Pedreira, a vocation school for construction workers. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Hiroshi joined the Rotary Club of São Paulo Sudeste in 2003. He is currently a member of the São Paulo-Aeroporto club, where he has served as club president (2011-12), and will be district governor in 2014-15. He enjoys the Foundation’s Matching Grants program, which allowed his club to work with clubs in Japan to donate an ambulance to a nursing home in São Paulo.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Hiroshi and Suma have been married for over 40 years. Suma is a university professor. She enjoys reading and walking around the city with Hiroshi. They have two children and four grandchildren.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='São Paulo-Aeroporto' ows_DistrictRI='4420' ows_RegionRI='São Paulo' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/HiroshiandSumaI.Shimuta/Shimuta Hiroshi.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='HiroshiandSumaI.Shimuta/HiroshiAndSumaShimuta.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Brazil' ows_CountryCodeRI='BR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='848' ows_LinkTitle='DongKurnLeeandYoungJaChung' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Dong Kurn Lee and Young Ja Chung' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Dong Kurn Lee spent part of grade school and many summers in the countryside village of Yangdong, Korea. He attended Yonsei University in Seoul, where he studied political science. He is the chairman of Bubang Co. Ltd. and Bubang Techron Co. Ltd., family businesses that manufacture electronics and home appliances in both Korea and China, and is a trustee of Busan College of Information Technology. In 2005, the president of Korea appointed D.K. international goodwill ambassador.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;D.K. joined the Rotary Club of Seoul Hangang in 1971. Following in the footsteps of his Rotarian father, he served as district governor in 1995-96. In addition to serving on and chairing numerous committees over the years, D.K. has served as RI director (2001-02), treasurer (2002-03), and president (2008-09). During his term as president, he focused on reducing child mortality. D.K. has also served as Rotary Foundation trustee (2003-06 and 2010-12) and will serve as trustee chair-elect in 2012-13 and trustee chair in 2013-14.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;D.K.’s wife, Young, enjoys accompanying him to Rotary events. Placing a high value on friendship, D.K. and Young like to attend dinner parties with colleagues and friends. They have four children.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Seoul Hangang' ows_DistrictRI='3650' ows_RegionRI='Seoul' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/DongKurnLeeandYoungJaChung/Lee Dong.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='849' ows_LinkTitle='SajjanandChandaGoenka' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Sajjan and Chanda Goenka' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Sajjan Goenka, who studied commerce in college, works as a readymade garment manufacturer and exporter. Previously, he worked for an aerated water bottler for over 30 years. He has served on many professional boards, including Panki Industries Association, Upper India Chamber of Commerce, Kanpur Productivity Council, and the Merchants’ Chamber of Uttar Pradesh.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sajjan joined the Rotary Club of Kanpur West in 1968. He was club president in 1977-78 and district governor in 1982-33. Using Matching Grants, he helped his club to establish the Rotary DG Goenka Blood Bank and also established the Sight On Wheels project, which provides cataract surgeries to people in rural areas. Sajjan is the recipient of The Rotary Foundation Citation for Meritorious Service and the RI Service Above Self Award.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sajjan and Chanda have been married for over 48 years. Chanda supports Sajjan’s Rotary responsibilities, and enjoys attending community service projects in their community. They have three children and four grandchildren. Sajjan and Chanda support The Rotary Foundation through the DG Goenka Endowment Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Bombay West' ows_DistrictRI='3140' ows_RegionRI='Maharashtra' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SajjanandChandaGoenka/Goenka Sajjan.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='SajjanandChandaGoenka/SajjanAndChandaGoenka.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='India' ows_CountryCodeRI='IN' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='850' ows_LinkTitle='JohnH.andA.RoseMoonSr.' ows_TitleDisplayRI='John H. and A. Rose Moon, Sr.' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;John H. Moon Sr. was born in Van Buren, Arkansas, USA. He received a bachelor’s degree in business with honors from Texas A&amp;amp;M University and became a certified public accountant (CPA) at age 21. He is the chairman, president, and director of Moon Credit Corp., chairman and president of Moon Capital Corp., and a partner at Moon and Associates. John is a member of three CPA societies and a past director of several Pasadena organizations committed to community improvement. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;John joined the Rotary Club of Pasadena, Texas, in 1970 and, as of 2012, has had 42 years of perfect club attendance. He has spent several years serving as his club’s Rotary Foundation chair. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;John and Rose have been married for over 50 years. Rose has been supportive of John’s Rotary career, often joining him at club meetings and district conferences. She enjoys reading and writing in her free time. The Moons have two sons and five grandchildren.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Pasadena' ows_DistrictRI='5890' ows_RegionRI='Texas' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JohnH.andA.RoseMoonSr./Moon John.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='JohnH.andA.RoseMoonSr./JohnAndRoseMoon.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='851' ows_LinkTitle='SangKooYunandEunSunYang' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Sang Koo Yun and Eun Sun Yang' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Sang Koo Yun was born in Seoul, Korea. He attended Syracuse University in Syracuse, New York. He has served as the CEO of Dongsuh Corporation, which manufactures architectural materials, since 1985. Sang Koo has volunteered his time on the Keep Mongolia Green project as well as the building of the Tumbi-Rotary Mother and Child Health Complex in Tanzania.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sang Koo joined the Rotary Club of Sae Hanyang in 1986. He served as club president (1991-92) and district governor (2004-05). An active committee member, he has served as: district Rotary world peace fellowships chair (2008-10), district Rotary Foundation chair (2010-13), and as a member of the Reach Out to Africa committee (2011-12).
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sang Koo has been married to Eun Sun Yang for over 32 years. A homemaker, Eun Sun enjoys volunteering as the director of operations for the Seoul Spring Festival Chamber Music and as the director of the Beautiful Store, a resale shop that uses its profit for charity work in the community. Sang Koo and Eun Sun have two children. They support The Rotary Foundation through the Sang Koo Yun and Eun Sun Yang Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Sae Hanyang' ows_DistrictRI='3650' ows_RegionRI='Seoul' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SangKooYunandEunSunYang/Yun Sang.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='852' ows_LinkTitle='HabilF.andNafisaKhorakiwala' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Habil F. and Nafisa Khorakiwala' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Habil Khorakiwala is the chairman of Wockhardt Group, a research-based health care organization that has five research centers and 21 manufacturing plants around the world.&amp;nbsp; He is also the chairman of Wockhardt Hospitals, a leading health care institute in India. He founded the Wockhardt Foundation, whose mission is to work with the underprivileged in India. Habil received his MS from Purdue University and attended the Advanced Management Program at the Harvard Business School.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Habil joined the Rotary Club of Bombay North in 1969. He served as club president in 1986 and as assistant governor in 2002. He has received a Rotary award for his Vocational Excellence. He enjoys working on Rotary projects that focus on improving access to water and health care. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Habil and his wife, Nafisa, have been married for over 43 years. Nafisa is the chair of WHARF, a platform for health care professionals to improve their knowledge about HIV/AIDS. Habil and Nafisa have three children, one who is a Rotarian.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Bombay North' ows_DistrictRI='3140' ows_RegionRI='Maharashtra' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/HabilF.andNafisaKhorakiwala/Khorakiwala H.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='HabilF.andNafisaKhorakiwala/HabilAndNafisaKhorakiwala.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='India' ows_CountryCodeRI='IN' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='853' ows_LinkTitle='SudhansuandMinaBhattacharyya' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Sudhansu and Mina Bhattacharyya' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Sudhansu Bhattacharyya was born in Murshidabad, West Bengal. A renowned cardiothoracic surgeon, he obtained his MBBS and MS in general surgery in Ahmedabad before moving to Mumbai to study cardiac surgery. He participated in a fellowship in the United States where he learned surgical techniques for the most complicated cases of coronary artery disease. Before entering into practice, he served as a full-time professor of cardiothoracic surgery at Sheth G.S. Medical College and KEM Hospital.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;A pioneer in his profession, Sudhansu often presents lectures, classes, and papers on his cases. He is credited with creating techniques and instruments that are vital to others in his field. He travels throughout India to teach others.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Sudhansu joined the Rotary Club of Bombay Central in 1974. Sudhansu&amp;#39;s wife, Mina, is a retired professor of gynecology. They enjoy international travel. Sudhansu and Mina have two children. They support The Rotary Foundation through the Sudhansu Bhattacharyya Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Bombay Central' ows_DistrictRI='3140' ows_RegionRI='Maharashtra' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SudhansuandMinaBhattacharyya/Bhattacharryya Sudhansu.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='SudhansuandMinaBhattacharyya/SudhansuAndMinaBhattacharyya.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='India' ows_CountryCodeRI='IN' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='854' ows_LinkTitle='StevenandIrisR.Laine' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Steven and Iris R. Laine' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Steven Laine was born in Sacramento, California, USA, and is a graduate of the American Institute of Baking. He is a retired food service executive and held management positions in the International Foodservice Manufacturers Association and U.S. Department of Agriculture. In addition to being a published author, he has been on executive committees of the Daily Bread Food Bank, Boy Scouts, Seafarers’ House and South Florida base commander of U.S. Submarine Veterans Inc.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Steve joined the Rotary Club of East Oakland, California, in 1954. He was later a board member of the Rotary Club of Chicago and of several clubs in Florida, including the Rotary Club of Boca Raton Sunset, one of three clubs chartered in his year as district governor in 1995-96. He has held numerous assignments in his Rotary career, including serving as a Permanent Fund National Advisor, and he received the Service Above Self Award in 2000 and the Citation for Meritorious Service in 2006.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Steve and Iris have been married for more than 40 years. Iris is a graduate of Florida Atlantic University, has an MDiv from Gettysburg Lutheran Seminary, is an ordained minister, and is author of three books. They have three children, six grandchildren, and 10 great-grandchildren.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Boca Raton Sunset' ows_DistrictRI='6930' ows_RegionRI='Florida' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/StevenandIrisR.Laine/Laine Steve.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='StevenandIrisR.Laine/StevenLaine.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='855' ows_LinkTitle='SeungRyongHanandHeeJongYou' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Seung Ryong Han and Hee Jong You' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Seung Ryong Han holds a doctorate in public health from Yeonsei University in Korea. He is the chairman of both the Cheongpa Scholarship Foundation and the Hankyungbeom Scholarship Foundation, which combined have provided more than US$164 million in scholarships to more than 570 students, as of 2012. Seung Ryong also has worked as an auditor for the Korean Chamber of Commerce and as chairman of the Weonju City Olympic Promotion Committee.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Seung Ryong is a charter member of the Rotary Club of Weonju, which he joined in 1963. He served as district governor in 1991-92. His favorite Rotary project is Team-Spirit Joint Operations, which is a partnership to develop the relationship between Korean and American Rotarians.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Seung Ryong and Hee Jong You have been married for over 60 years. Hee Jong enjoys music and participating in community service activities. Seung Ryong and Hee Jong have three children and two grandchildren.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Weonju' ows_DistrictRI='3730' ows_RegionRI='Gangweon' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/SeungRyongHanandHeeJongYou/Han Seung.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='SeungRyongHanandHeeJongYou/SeungRuongHanAndHeeJongYou.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='856' ows_LinkTitle='HongJooYoonandKyungHeeLee1' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Hong-Joo Yoon and Kyung Hee Lee' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Hong-Joo Yoon was born in Hapcheon, Korea. He attended Gyeonghoo University Medical School, where he earned his medical license in plastic and reconstructive surgery. He served as chair of the Busan Ulsan branch of the Korea Plastic Surgeon Association in 1999-2000, chair of the Busan Plastic Surgeons in Practice Association, and vice chair of the Korean Plastic Surgeons in Practice Association from 2002 to 2004. 
&lt;br&gt;Hong-Joo joined the Rotary Club of Busan-Hang in 1998, serving as president in 2004-05 and district governor in 2010-11. He transferred to the Rotary Club of Busan Mugunghwa in 2011. 
&lt;br&gt;Hong-Joo is married to Kyung Hee Lee, who is a member of the Rotary Club of Pusan-Tongbaek. She works as a pharmacist and enjoys photography in her spare time. Hong-Joo and Kyung Hee have two children. They support The Rotary Foundation through the Hong-Joo Yoon Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Busan Mugunghwa' ows_DistrictRI='3660' ows_RegionRI='Busan' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/HongJooYoonandKyungHeeLee1/Yoon Hong Joo.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='HongJooYoonandKyungHeeLee1/HongJooYoonAndKyungHeeLee.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='857' ows_LinkTitle='EungJongYooandHeeSookChung' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Eung Jong Yoo and Hee Sook Chung' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Eung Jong Yoo was born in Chungbuk, Korea. He earned a master’s degree in administration from Seoul National University and works in the service distribution industry. Among his community activities, Eung is the chairman of the Korean Cultural Foundation, Chungbuk Province Baseball Association, and Cheongju Athletics Foundation; vice president of Chungbuk Province Administration; and president of the Sharing Love Association.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Eung joined the Rotary Club of Cheongju in 1981 and served as president (1992-93) and district governor (2001-02). His favorite Rotary club project was providing free medical services in Vietnam in 2005. He enjoys supporting The Rotary Foundation because it allows him to help people in need all around the world. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Eung and his wife, Hee Sook Chung, have been married for over 30 years. Hee Sook also works in the service distribution industry and enjoys reading, golfing, and hiking. Eung and Hee Sook have two sons.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Cheongju' ows_DistrictRI='3740' ows_RegionRI='Chungcheongbug' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/EungJongYooandHeeSookChung/Yoo Eung.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='858' ows_LinkTitle='KyunKimandHyeSukJeong' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Kyun Kim and Hye Suk Jeong' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Kyun Kim graduated from the University of Leeds in England with a degree in industrial economics. He is the CEO of Mars Co. Ltd., which produces chemical products. In addition to his professional endeavors, Kyun serves as executive vice president of his high school’s alumni association. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Kyun joined the Rotary Club of Busan-Dongrae in 1993 and served as its president in 2006-07. Kyun served as district governor in 2011-12. He received the RI Presidential Citation award in 2008. His favorite Rotary Foundation project has been to provide a digital X-ray machine for use in diagnosing tuberculosis to the nonprofit Green Doctors hospital in the Kaesŏng Industrial Region.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Kyun and Hye Suk have been married for over 35 years. Hye Suk is skilled in the traditional Korean fan dance, and she loves music. Kyun and Hye Suk have two children and two grandchildren. Kyun and Hye Suk support The Rotary Foundation through the Kyun Kim Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Busan-Dongrae' ows_DistrictRI='3660' ows_RegionRI='Busan' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/KyunKimandHyeSukJeong/Kim Kyun.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='859' ows_LinkTitle='InChulParkandHaiSoonBae' ows_TitleDisplayRI='In Chul Park and Hai Soon Bae' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;In Chul Park was born in Seoul, Korea, and graduated from Yonsei University. He is the chairman of Leehan Corporation, a global automotive parts supplier, and has served on the boards of the Korea Trade Association and the Korea Auto Industry Cooperative.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;In Chul is a charter member of the Rotary Club of Anyang. He later joined the Anyang East club and has served as club president (1981) and district governor (2002-03). He participated in a Group Study Exchange in 2006. After several years as a member of the Permanent Fund Committee for Korea, he became the 2012-13 vice chair. In Chul received The Rotary Foundation’s Citation for Meritorious Service in 2005.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;In Chul Park and Hai Soon Bae have been married for over 39 years. They support The Rotary Foundation through the In Chul Park Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Anyang East' ows_DistrictRI='3750' ows_RegionRI='Gyeonggi' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/InChulParkandHaiSoonBae/Park In.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='860' ows_LinkTitle='YongKeukShin' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Yong Keuk Shin' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Yong Keuk was born in Seoul, Korea. He attended the Hankuk University of Foreign Studies, where he focused on learning foreign trade. He is the chairman of EURO Trading Co. Ltd. Yong Keuk is the son of a former district governor, and due to his father’s strong influence, he joined the Seoul Namsan club in 1987. He has served as club president (2010-11). His favorite club activity is to provide volunteer medical assistance for Chaoxianzu residents, Chinese people of Korean descent, in Yanbian, China.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Yong Keuk married Chun-Sun Park in 1968. She operates an art gallery. Yong Keuk and Chun-Sun have three children. They support The Rotary Foundation through the Yong Keuk Shin Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Seoul Namsan' ows_DistrictRI='3650' ows_RegionRI='Seoul' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/YongKeukShin/Shin Yong.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='861' ows_LinkTitle='AlandRuthBraswell' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Al and Ruth Braswell' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;The oldest of six children, Al Braswell was born in Texas and grew up on farms there and in Oklahoma. He left home at age 15 to start 16 years of self-supported university attendance, which led to five academic degrees, including a doctorate in ecology. Putting his education to use, he constructed the first world-recognized, earth-friendly, steel-reinforced-concrete monolithic residential dome complex. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;But Al’s professional life was largely dedicated to teaching. He taught at public schools in California and Oregon and as a university professor in Maryland and Utah, Chile, and Venezuela. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Al was encouraged to join the Rotary Club of Yucaipa in 1990 by Ruth, his late wife, who was a member of the Rotary Club of Jurupa. They cochaired District 5330’s polio eradication fundraising campaigns for 15 years, and participated in two National Immunization Days, in Ghana and India. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;After retiring from teaching, Al acquired a small chain of residential treatment facilities for adults and seniors, in California. He is an avid hiker, and he sings in a barbershop and gospel quartet.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Yucaipa and Jurupa' ows_DistrictRI='5330' ows_RegionRI='California' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/AlandRuthBraswell/Braswell Al.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='AlandRuthBraswell/AlBraswell.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Chair Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='862' ows_LinkTitle='JimandDonnaPhilips' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Jim and Donna Philips' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Jim Philips was born in Edinburgh, Scotland, and moved to the United States, where he attended the University of Georgia for his business administration degree. Before retiring, he worked in the real estate financial services sector, selling his Atlanta-based firm, Hatfield Philips, in 2003 and his London-based Hatfield Philips firm in 2004. He is active in the community and is a trustee for the Columbia Theological Seminary.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Donna Philips was born in Walla Walla, Washington, and attended the University of Georgia, where she received a bachelor’s degree in special education. Before retiring, Donna taught special education classes in Atlanta. She is an active volunteer with the DeKalb Rape Crisis Center and the Frazer Center for Children and Adults with Disabilities.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Jim joined the Rotary Club of Decatur in 1984. He served as club president in 2001-02 and assistant governor in 2004-05. Donna was made an honorary member of the Decatur club in 2010. The polio eradication effort is one their favorite Foundation projects, and she and Jim traveled to India for a National Immunization Day in 2006, a journey that was captured in the Rotary film “The Last Hurdle.”&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Decatur' ows_DistrictRI='6900' ows_RegionRI='Georgia' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/JimandDonnaPhilips/Philips Jim and Donna.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='United States' ows_CountryCodeRI='US' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='863' ows_LinkTitle='DukSamLeeandHyunSukJang' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Duk-Sam Lee and Hyun-Suk Jang' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Duk-Sam Lee was born in Seoul, Korea. He has built a successful career in the manufacturing industry and is the CEO of Sunseong Company. Duk-Sam is also the chairman of the Jingeon High School Alumni Association, vice chairman of Jingeon Police Station’s Safety Assurance Foundation, and director of the Gyeonggi Province Chamber of Commerce and the Namyangju City Athletic Association. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Duk-Sam joined the Rotary Club of Namyangju-Jingeon in 2005. He has served as club president three times (2006-09). He served as assistant governor in 2010-11. He enjoys working on service projects with his fellow club members, particularly projects assisting the elderly and providing home repair services to those in need.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Hyun-Suk Jang, who is also a member of the Rotary Club of Namyangju-Jingeon, is self-employed. Duk-Sam and Hyun-Suk have been married for more than 25 years, and they have a son and a daughter.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Namyangju-Jingeon' ows_DistrictRI='3600' ows_RegionRI='Gyeonggi' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/DukSamLeeandHyunSukJang/LeeDukSam.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Korea' ows_CountryCodeRI='KR' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='864' ows_LinkTitle='MayChinMeiLu' ows_TitleDisplayRI='May Chin-Mei Lu' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;May Chin-Mei Lu was born in Kaohsuing, Taiwan. She completed her executive master’s in business administration through National Taipei University. An employee for many years at Fortune Motors Co. Ltd., the largest Mitsubishi dealership in Taiwan, May worked in several areas, including service, human resources, and marketing. She also served as a board member. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;A charter member of the first all-female Rotary club in District 3480, May has been very active in Rotary, serving as club president (2003-04) and chair of the District 3480 Conference (2011-12). She has also participated on numerous club committees. May is extremely proud of the installation of an intelligent library in the local community, a project that she lead.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;May has two sons and both have traveled with her for Rotary-sponsored projects. She supports The Rotary Foundation through the Chin-Mei (&amp;quot;May&amp;quot;) Lu Rotary Peace Fellowship.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei Fu-Jung' ows_DistrictRI='3480' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/MayChinMeiLu/Lu May Chin-Mei.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='MayChinMeiLu/MayChinMeuLu.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='865' ows_LinkTitle='ComputerChiuLinandJasmineChiu' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Computer Chiu-Lin and Jasmine Chiu' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Computer Chiu-Lin Chiu was born in Kaohsiung, Taiwan. He studied chemical engineering at Chung Yuan University in Taiwan. He is the CEO of Unixtar Technology Inc., a manufacturer of computer cables, and serves as director for Space Shuttle Hi-Tech Co. Ltd. and Favor Laser Co. Ltd. He is active within the community and is chairman of the Taiwan affiliate of the Drikung Kagyu Association and the New Taipei Tainan County Association.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Computer joined the Rotary Club of Feitsui in 1996. His leadership in Rotary includes club president (1996-97) and district governor (2013-14). His favorite Rotary projects are those that involve humanitarian work. Passionate about world peace, Computer hopes that Rotary one day will help promote peace between Taiwan and China.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Computer is married to Jasmine Chiu, who enjoys cooking and volunteering. Jasmine also supports Computer’s Rotary work, often attending club and district activities. They have two daughters and one granddaughter. The couple have chosen to support the Foundation through the Computer Chiu-Lin and Jasmine Chiu Rotary Peace Center Fellowship Endowment Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Feitsui' ows_DistrictRI='3480' ows_RegionRI='Feitsui' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/ComputerChiuLinandJasmineChiu/Lin Computer Chiu.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='ComputerChiuLinandJasmineChiu/JasmineChiuAndComputerChiu.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='866' ows_LinkTitle='AngelaMingChuLuLeeandSteveChenTaiLee' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Angela Ming-Chu Lu Lee and Steve Chen-Tai Lee' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Angela Ming-Chu Lu Lee was born in Taipei, Taiwan, and graduated from Ming Chuan University. She works in the construction and land development field and has developed almost 30 office and residential buildings in downtown Taipei. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Angela is a member of the Rotary Club of Taipei Chang An and served as the charter club president in 2003-04. Her favorite Rotary Foundation programs are those involving education, and she is enthusiastic about the Matching Grant program. Angela finds that working with Rotary clubs overseas not only offers opportunities for service but also helps enhance communication between countries.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Steve Chen-Tai Lee, who also works in construction and land development, is a member of the Rotary Club of Taipei North. In addition to his Rotary service, he enjoys playing golf, reading, and traveling. Angela and Steve have been married for over 40 years. They have a daughter, who is a Rotarian; two sons; and a grandson.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei Chang An, and the Rotary Club of Taipei North' ows_DistrictRI='3520' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/AngelaMingChuLuLeeandSteveChenTaiLee/Lee Angela Ming-Chu and Steve_Chen-Tai.jpg' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='867' ows_LinkTitle='J.B.andMarleneKamdar' ows_TitleDisplayRI='J.B. and Marlene Kamdar' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;J.B. Kamdar was born in Mumbai, India. After finishing his undergraduate studies, he joined his family business, Nadi Airtechnics, a manufacturer of agricultural pump sets, in 1969. In 1974, in collaboration with British, German, and American companies, the company diversified into industrial fans and cooling equipment. J.B. is the managing director of TCF-Nadi Industrial Fans Pvt. Ltd. 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;J.B. joined Rotary in 1995 and served as his club’s president in 1999-2000. He has served Rotary as district governor (2006-07) and member of the RI Finance Committee and the Permanent Fund Committee for India. He is a recipient of the 2010 RI Service Above Self Award.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;J.B. and Marlene married in 1977. An educational psychologist and counselor, Marlene founded and is the principal of the Saraswathi Kendra Learning Centre for Children, a school for children with learning disabilities. She enjoys sewing, traveling, and the theater. J.B. and Marlene support The Rotary Foundation through the Marlene and J.B. Kamdar Endowed Fund.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Madras' ows_DistrictRI='3230' ows_RegionRI='Tamil Nadu' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/J.B.andMarleneKamdar/Kamdar Jayendra.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='J.B.andMarleneKamdar/JbAndMarleneKamdar.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='India' ows_CountryCodeRI='IN' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
   <z:row ows_ID='868' ows_LinkTitle='DatoNgKimPohAmkoandLucilleHuang' ows_TitleDisplayRI='Dato’ Ng Kim-Poh Amko and Lucille Huang' ows_BiographyRI='&lt;div&gt;Dato’ Ng Kim-Poh Amko was born in Melaka, Malaysia. He earned a bachelor’s degree in international business at National Chengchi University in Taipei, Taiwan, and an MBA at Tulane University in New Orleans, Louisiana, USA. He is the chairman of AMKO Industrial, a manufacturer of metal and rubber parts, and AMKO SOLARA, a manufacturer of energy-efficient lighting. He serves as a board supervisor at the Taipei Lifeline Association and is president of the World Association of YongChun.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Amko joined the Rotary Club of Taipei Southgate in 1991. His leadership in Rotary includes serving as club president (2001-02) and district governor (2013-14). He has represented his Rotary club on many Matching Grant projects that involve providing aid to children.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Amko married Lucille Huang in 1975. In addition to helping with the management of financial affairs in Amko’s businesses, Lucille enjoys participating in community events. Their two sons are instrumental in the family business, and have participated in Harvard University’s Family Business Management Program with Amko.&lt;/div&gt;' ows_ClubNameRI='Taipei Southgate' ows_DistrictRI='3520' ows_RegionRI='Taipei' ows_Image1PathRI='Donors/DatoNgKimPohAmkoandLucilleHuang/Huang Amko Kim-Poh.jpg' ows_Video1PathRI='DatoNgKimPohAmkoandLucilleHuang/LucilleHuangAndDatoAmko.mp4' ows_CountryNameRI='Taiwan' ows_CountryCodeRI='TW' ows_DonorLevelRI='Donor Levels/AKS Trustee Circle.png' />
</rs:data>
</xml>
